很_心你找我
- I'm so... - I'm so glad you called.
我很高d有空
I'm so glad you were free.
天啊,被你到了
God, I love your eyes.
那F在呢?
Okay, now what?
套上我的老二吧
Cup my balls.
好啊,@我的
- Okay, yes. - All right. I can do that.
噢!M砹,_始了
- Oh! There it is. - There we go.
真是爽
That feels good.
就知道
You know what to do.
@影,慢一c
Okay, you know what? Slow it down, slow it down.
慢一c
Okay. Slow it down.
不吧?
There we go. How's that?
柔柔,不也很爽?
That's good, nice and slow. See? Doesn't that feel good?
可是我想砜斓
Yeah. No, I want to go fast.
- 你想快的? - 快的
You want to go fast? Fast.
Yeah. No...
太爽了
Oh, yeah. That feels good.
Oh, Yeah.
Yeah.
你知道我想…
Okay. You know what? I think...
我的奏不搭哦
I think maybe we are on different rhythms here.
我做了,死我了
I was having a nightmare. I was so scared.
早安
Good morning.
真是正c
You look beautiful.
不,我的幼右欢êK
No, I'm sure I look terrible.
才起床耶,你壅f笑?
I just woke up. Are you kidding?
肯定活像鬼
I'm sure I'm a mess.
睡了一夜
You slept over.
]e
I did.
我想我要"^夜"l款
I thought we had a rule against that.
噢?
Oh.
我_玩笑的
I'm kidding. Oh.
- 真好笑 - _玩笑的
That was funny. I'm kidding.
一早就@NL趣
You're funny in the morning.
- 我喜gc相 - 是喔?
I like hanging out with you. Oh. Yeah.
我也鄹你相,我想我可以^得很融洽
I love hanging out with you. I think we get along really well
而且你真性感
and you're so sexy.
我知道
I know.
我有忙不完的工作
I just have a lot coming up at work
所以不能信口_河
and I don't want to make promises I can't keep.
懂我f的吧?是明人
You know what I mean? I know you do.
,我有相同的共R
Yeah. We're on the same page.
我也不想在此r定下,就明v
I'm not looking for a relationship right now, either. Let's just say that.
不管你想怎,我都意…
Whatever you wanna... I can do...
我渭c,不像e的女孩
I'd rather just... I like simple... I'm not like other girls.
我不喜g"我的男友吧",除非你f"好"
I'm not like, "Be my boyfriend!" Unless you were like, "Yeah!"
反倒喜g"也S吧"
Then I'd be like, "Maybe."
是不要吧
Mmm. But let's not.
我也不喜g那
I don't want that either.
真擂,我真的要s走了
Wow, this is so awkward. I really want you to leave,
不得不出言不d
but I don't know how to say it without sounding like a dick.
快!手放耳後 J真c,@是抑P起坐
Come on! Hands behind your heads! Let's go! Sit-ups!
你就像一P培根
You're looking like pieces of bacon on a plate.
f心死了!油的味道!
It's disgusting! I smell the fat!
- 他到我了 - 我也是
- He scares me. - Me, too.
但他是^佳的右
But he's an excellent motivator.
]e
That's true.
在看哪?
What are you looking at?
挫屎,他lF我了,天啊
Oh, Shit, he sees us. Oh, God.
Hey! Hey!
如果想W
If you want to take this class,
就必UX
you're going to have to pay for it
就像@群臭娘!
like the rest of these bitches!
什N,在跳舞? 在公@…的舞蹈n?
What, are you dancing? In the park... Dance class?
那算哪T子的舞蹈,不是硖舞的!
You are not dancing. You are not dancing in the park!
- 快W! - 白吃白喝
- Go, go, go, go! - Freeloaders!
我^去了喔
I'm coming over there.
- 他有跟? - ^去了喔!
- Is he coming? - I'm coming after you!
抱歉,洛尼,我手^o
Sorry, Rodney. We're on a budget.
e[了啦!才12K耶!
- Oh, come on! - It's only 12 bucks!
天啊!
Oh, my God!
兔!敢o我偷n
Come on! You fucking freeloaders.
- 我真是了 - 我知道
We are out of our minds. I know.
]PS,很c幸我的猿
That's okay. I'm so glad that we got to do this.
因橐葬岷孟穸家不到了
I feel like I haven't seen you in forever.
我在芝加哥住很久了啊
Mmm. I've been in Chicago a lot.
我知道,睡在小道道的Ce
I know. Sleeping at Dougie's house.
只是方便工作
Well, it's just closer to work.
跟他的戆?
How is it going with him anyway?
不缘,我是指^得去
I don't know. I mean, it's fine,
只是X得他最近u行uh
but I just feel like he's been distant lately.
我也不清楚…
And I don't know...
他都叫我"老兄"
He calls me "dude" a lot.
e想太多
That doesn't mean anything.
我X得]事的
I think everything is fine.
我不@N想
I don't know. Anyway,
昨晚在做什N?
what did you do last night?
Umm...
昨晚在忙什N?
What did you do last night?
打算不我知道
You are not telling me something.
我跟泰德小片刻
I hung out with Ted for a little bit.
- 我就知道! - 我^的很_心
I knew it! We had fun.
- 真的很_心 - @我就不懂了
It was fun. Here's what I don't like about it.
每次^他之後都很自悔
You hate yourself after you see him, every time.
每次到@,就一副屎面
And then we go through this, and then you feel like shit,
好像不去
and it's almost like you're doing it
就Σ黄鹱约
because you feel bad about yourself.
他很晚才打o我,去就f聊
He called me late, and we hung out.
又]什N大不了,重c是玩的很_心
It wasn't a big deal. And you know what? It was fun.
跟他上床
Ew! You had sex with him.
我^了成人之夜
We had an adult sleepover.
有"他"塞在嘴e^一夜?
Ooh. Did you let him sleep over in your mouth?
- 安妮 - Σ黄
Annie! I'm sorry!
- 太不可思h了 - 他一直把它靠在我旁
You're unbelievable. He kept putting it near my face.
男人都@Π?
They do that, don't they?
有何必要?好我服
Why do they do that? Let us offer.
要是我不服…
If we don't offer...
把它巴走的
Please. You're supposed to slap it away.
我o能榱
I couldn't.
- 不想瞪著它看 - ]e
You don't want to look right at it.
No.
太唐突了,就好像…
It's too aggressive. It's like...
"你好"
"Hello."
烙印在我X海e
That's my impression.
MX子的B蛋?
Those are the balls?
,我也想D移心思
Yeah. I'm trying to make it round,
但我就是瞿l
but I can't because I have elbows.
因樗太辣了
He is so hot, though.
我明白形容他惹人鄣幼
Look, I know you say he's cute and all that stuff,
但事後都很狼N,知道?
but it makes you feel like shit, you know?
分明就是"女王不挑"
You're a total catch, and any guy
任何男人都能打芳心
would be psyched to be your man.
找一
You should just make room
\心Υ的人
for somebody who is nice to you.
知道,他很真\
You know what? He's honest!
他一五一十地f
He told me that we are what we are
我只是玩玩,我也欣然接受
and we're just having fun. And I like that.
他敢X,那王八蛋
He also told you that you need dental work. He's an asshole.
我不需要看牙X
I don't need dental work.
]e
You're right.
我的牙X]有}
There is nothing wrong with my teeth.
真是美呆了
You are so beautiful.
- 意嫁o我? - 意
Will you marry me? Yes.
- 我 - 我
I love you.
我今天不想去工作
I don't want to go to work today. Mmm-mmm.
看看泰瑞打淄o我了
Let's see how many times Terry's called me.
HH15通!
Oh! Only 15!
泰瑞你知道?
You know what, Terry? I don't want
我不想去拿你的猴子台,抱歉了!
to pick up your monkey lamps. Sorry!
猴子台?
Monkey lamps?
真想永hx_那神精病老
Ugh. I cannot wait to never work for a psychopath again.
安妮!
Oh! Annie!
Σ黄,我不走砻飞街的
I'm sorry. I should have gone down Mason.
我x在不景獾r候_,也真蛱斓
Well, I'm the genius that opened a bakery during the recession.
}不在蛋糕,安妮
They were good cakes, Annie.
xx
Thank you.
快看e,看e
Come on. Look away, look away, look away.
有喜g的款式?
Do you have any ideas of styles?
不知道,你X得呢,小心肝?
Oh, I don't know. What do you think, honey?
Q定就好
Whatever you want.
看看你一起的幼
Look at how you guys are making this decision together.
真是甜蜜,彼此相郯?
That's sweet. You guys love each other, huh?
- ]e - ]e
Yeah. Yeah.
太甜蜜了,那只是一ㄒ滑F
Ohh! That's sweet. That will go away.
永h不能相信任何人
You cannot trust anybody, ever.
特e是有H密PS的
Especially someone you're in a relationship with.
因檫@N人找同居
'Cause they're living with you, you don't
s不JR@位枕人,很恐怖
know who you're sleeping next to. It is scary.
瞧瞧他,甚至不是|方人
I mean, look at him. He may not even be Asian.
很恐怖地
It is scary.
那你想看婚戒?
So did you guys want to look at these engagement rings?
- 再看看 - ]P}
We're going to browse. Okay, sure.
我等著
I'll be here.
xx光R
Thank you.
那是怎N回事?
What was that about?
]事,他正好要x_去e逛
Umm, nothing. They had to run. They had to go somewhere.
也y怪,兼uK身福幸福指南
And no wonder. You're selling lifelong happiness.
不用逢人就f
You're not telling everyone about your problems
男朋友的事
and how your boyfriend left you,
也S婚姻是l出路
and maybe marriage will work out.
表F出"凼怯a"的表情
Show me your "love is eternal" face.
e,那是2年,多4年 那不叫永a
No, that's two years, four years tops. That is not eternal.
卡哇,可以麻^硪幌?
Kahlua, can you come over here for a second, please?
怎N啦,?
What's up, Don-Don?
@b取的最好
You make up the best nicknames.
就不用b,因榭哇正是咖啡酒
You don't need a nickname because Kahlua is so delicious.
e控告我碰喔
Don't sue me for touching you.
秀一下"凼怯a"的表情
Show Annie your "love is eternal" face.
@叫痛
That looks like you have menstrual cramps.
非常感x,卡哇
Thank you so much, Kahlua.
就不能多WW卡哇?
Now, why can't you be more like Kahlua?
我M力了
Look, I'm trying really hard.
那就更努力
You've just got to try harder.
之所以能保住工作
The whole reason you have got this job, Annie,
是令堂在戒酒o名助我,我在回笏
is because your mom is my sponsor in AA, and I'm doing her a favor.
我懂了
I understand.
W斯卡,回去位
Oscar, get back to work.
你不躲在台後
You shouldn't be behind the counter.
安德,你不用爸爸了
Andrew, you are not the father!
太好了
That's great. Yeah.
快停,e跳了
Stop that. Don't do that.
嘿,布恩
Hey, Brynn.
嘿,室友
Oh, hey, roomie.
- 猜我今天怎N了? - 怎?
Guess what happened to me today. Hmm. What?
- 免M的刺青 - 什N?
I got a free tattoo. You did what?
- y以置信,那人f"想刺青?" - 巧吧
I could not believe it. The guy said, "Do you want a tattoo?"
Just a random...
- ,他打_箱 - 不吧
Yeah, opened up the side of his van. No.
他f"免X唷",我f"好啊"
He said, "it's for free!" And I said, "Sure."
- f好? -
You said yes? Yeah!
看,有看到吧?
Yeah. Look. See here?
刺什N?
What is it?
看到吧?
See that?
我的啊,布恩
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, Brynn!
是老墨酒x
It's a Mexican drinking worm.
美洲原住民代表"醉了"的符
It's a Native American symbol meaning "wasted."
布恩,你知道@…
Okay, Brynn, just so you know, it's...
- 嗨,吉 - 你好?
Gil, hi. Hello. How are you?
你有看到你妹的刺青?乐馗腥
Have you seen your sister's tattoo? It's really infected.
放c冰K就好c了
Better get a little bit of ice on it.
,好c
Yeah, a little bit.
敷上冷龆拱
Stick some frozen peas on there.
- 不痛 - 好吧
Yeah. It can't hurt. All right.
那我就不多述
So, I just wanted a quick word.
明天就要U房租了
You know that tomorrow the rent is due.
我_始收到薪Y
I was getting my check, and I wondered
我想我也可以拿到的吧?
if I could get your check, too?
我在X了
Yes. I'm getting the money.
_步慢了些
It's been a little slow.
要把整袋敷在l炎
You have to keep it in the bag and put the bag on it.
那支票呢?
So, the check?
- 好的,好的 -
Yes. Yes. Yeah.
- 因榍r似乎不容再拖欠了 - 了解
Because it's a kind of, like, "needing it today"-type situation.
R上就
It's coming.
- 哪位? - 我!
- Who is it? - Me!
哪位?
Who is it?
天啊,要快c,的怪居
Oh, my God. Hurry up, your creepy neighbor asked me
又邀我想不想看新
if I wanted to watch the news again.
抱歉,他真的很f
Sorry. He is so gross.
- M - 我湍拿sI
- Please, come on in. - Let me take your magazines.
g迎光RsI白酒派
Welcome to the magazine and wine party. Ooh!
坐
Have a seat.
能砦艺娴姆浅ｉ_心
I'm very happy that you are here.
- 什N? - 因槲蚁氤蕴O果
What? Because I want to eat an apple.
想睃cO果?
Would you like some apple?
- 那是什N - 我婚了
What is that? I got engaged.
- 什N? - 他昨晚_口的
What? He asked me last night.
- 不吧? - ]e!
What? I know!
y怪他要b神弄鬼
That's why he's been acting so weird
他演技太了,以|窗事l
'cause he's a terrible liar, and he thought he was gonna blow it.
所以就不理我
He was ignoring me and I thought
我以樗想分手
he was going to break up with me.
我的天啊
Oh, my gosh.
我的天啊!
Oh, my gosh!
Π!
I know!
小莉!
Lil!
我@魂未定
I'm shocked, still.
但很_心,很y相信吧?
But I'm happy. Can you believe this?
我的天啊,我好
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, I just got hot.
真的?]事吧
You did? Are you okay?
]事,我的身w在j汗
Yes. My pits are sweating.
- 胃在痛,又 - 什N意思?
My stomach hurts. I'm hot. What does that mean?
天啊!怎N?
Oh, my God! What is happening?
不缘,我戴上戒指了
I don't know. I'm wearing a ring.
我也o法相信
I can't believe it.
小莉,要Y婚了
Lil, you're getting married.
我要Y婚了
I'm getting married.
⑹俏业陌槟
And you'll be my maid of honor.
天啊,x不容o!
God, of course I will!
- 一定超_心的 - 一定玩翻天
It will be super fun. It's gonna be really fun.
,我可以一起策
Yeah. You know, we can plan everything together.
天啊!策的婚Y
My God! Planning your wedding...
_定可以?
Are you sure you're up for it?
我知道@是人所y
I know it's a lot to ask and to put on your plate.
正面R危急r刻,忙到不可_交
And you're going through a tricky time, and you're super-busy...
- 安o - 太人所y
Stop. It's a lot to ask.
- 安o - 遵命
Stop. Okay.
]PS,我更缝,不太超^
It's fine. And I'm more than happy to do it, and it's not too much.
你瞧!我的未婚夫黼
Oh! Look at that. It's my fiancé calling.
的未婚夫
Oh, your fiancé.
,怎N啦?
Hi, baby, what's up?
是安妮,我才跟她v完! Π,她非常_心
it's Annie. I just told her! Yeah, she's so happy.
我不_心!
No, I'm not!
"",她f的
"Yay," she said.
怎,?
What, baby?
我知道,我也想你
I know, I miss you, too.
,再1小r就可以到你了
Yeah, I'll meet you in an hour.
我也勰
I love you, too.
Wow.
薇Z娜Z德
Wynonna Judd.
的真魃
That's really good.
@些名媛真是火冒三丈
Painting those giant bangs was a royal pain in my can.
牙X白喔!真想把她成]嘴
And those teeth! I should have painted her mouth shut.
可以先Qb?我快s不上婚派α
Can you just get dressed? We're gonna be late for the engagement party.
- H鄣,忘了跟f - 怎?
Oh, I forgot to tell you, honey. What?
- 忘了告V - 怎?
Forgot to tell you. What?
我今晚登戒酒o名演v了,非去不可
I signed up to speak at AA tonight, and I just have to.
不吧,!
Mom! No.
我忘了,我的e,抱歉
I forgot. I'm sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
我一直叮不去的
I keep telling you, you're not supposed to go to those things.
又不是酒鬼
You're not an alcoholic.
就因槲奈春茸磉^
Only because I've never had a drink.
- 什N? - 那e能⒌先诵
What? They are inspiring.
我正好到一t故事,坐吧!
There is this one story I've just got to tell you. Sit down.
好吧
Okay.
@位要靠吹喇叭戆l的男士
This gentleman
who started blow-jobbing to get crack. His name is Marvin Johnson...
叫R文 森
- ,匿名 - 好,不明v
Mom, anonymous. You keep... It's no names. Okay, okay.
重,叫什NR文的
Forget it. Marvin J. Whatever.
- 聿患傲 - 他後沓槟型娼
Too late. Well, he became a gay prostitute.
他lF他要男的屁眼
And he realized that he had hit his bottom.
然後我就想,女
And I have been thinking, honey,
@也S就是低潮
that maybe this is your bottom.
我告V,遇到低潮是好事
I'm telling you, hitting bottom is a good thing.
因榉O泰
Because there's nowhere to go but up.
- Π? - ,是@N教的
Right? Yep. That's what you say.
- 是喜 - ]e
Yeah, a positive message. Yeah.
,xx的打
Yeah. Thanks for the pep talk, Mom.
H鄣,Sr候命
Honey. Anytime, anytime.
好啦,我也自去莉莉安的派α
All right. I guess I'm going to Lillian's party by myself, then.
e在我面前f自行
Don't talk to me about being by yourself.
我一向愍往
I go everywhere by myself.
多那位D,阿芭
Thanks to that new whore, Barb.
- ,拜 - 我也不想
Mom, come on. No, I don't like to say it.
他都Y婚12年了
They've been married 12 years.
,但她是u
Okay. But she's still a whore.
而且在桶晚迎接他,先摸U~
I'm sure she greets him in the evening, beaver first.
我不想聊@
I don't want to think about that.
我敢f她是跟老爸上床才I到的
I bet she got that car by giving your dad something sexually.
因橛幸徽形也桓以
'Cause there was one thing I would never do,
而阿芭F定超
and I'm sure Barb is a champion at it.
我不想知道
I don't want to know.
- 那招叫"公uj母u" - 想然耳
It's called a "chicken coop." Of course it is.
先尼嵬ラ_始啄
You start at the back and you peck your way
像Я穗u喙前往啄
to the front like you have a beak.
最後嘴巴含著2wB蛋
And then you end up with two eggs in your mouth.
真是f心
That's gross.
但我_定老爸酷
Well, I'm sure your dad likes it.
也是啦,他自小在r鲩L大
Of course, he grew up on a farm.
好吧
Okay.
_定不搬砀我住?
You sure you don't want to move in with me?
,心I了,但k不到
Mom, thanks, but no way.
T都]有?
No way in hell. Yeah?
,多x
No, thanks.
- 考]一下 - 好啦
Think about it. Okay.
不需另ぷ√
You don't need your own place.
- 我倒是喜g - 了解
Yeah, I Kind of do. Okay.
- 好啦,我要走了 - 好吧
All right, I'm going to go. All right.
鬼了
Holy shit.
泊小弟,@下好啦
Ohh. Valet. Perfect.
抱歉,需要清理
Sorry. Needs a wash.
你得多l状
You have to punch it a few times.
安妮!
Annie!
我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
- 天啊,莉莉安 - Π
Oh, my God, Lillian. I know.
的婚派不太F了?
This is your engagement party. Isn't that crazy?
真是富堂皇
It's so beautiful.
小道的老竟然是@e的T
I can't believe Dougie's boss is a member here.
他的pH也是,所以小道也是吧
I know, and his parents, too. And Dougie, I guess.
啊,然後我也是了
Gosh, and me, I guess, too, now.
我去候其他的H友吧
Come on, let's go say hi to the rest of the bridal party!
得我的堂姐塔?
You remember my cousin Rita?
- 塔 - 安妮
Rita. Annie.
高中I就]^了
I haven't seen you since you graduated high school.
她有3小孩
She has three kids now.
- 3男生 - 他非常可
- Three boys. - They're so cute.
是非常可,但到了一定年o
They are cute, but when they reach that age,
就很f心
they are disgusting.
w味,嵴痴车
They smell, they are sticky,
_始胡言yZ
they say things that are horrible,
有精液沾了到都是
and there is semen all over everything, okay?
不舒服
Disgusting.
它把毛毯一分槎
I cracked a blanket in half.
- 懂我的明白吧? - 懂
Do you get where I'm going with that? I do.
把毛毯一分槎
I cracked it in half.
什N?
What?
安妮,@位是卡,我的同事
Annie, this is Becca, my friend from work.
一同出生入死
We are in the trenches together.
- 嗨,幸了 - 好?
Hey. it's great to meet you. Hey, how are you?
幸
Nice to meet you.
@是我先生,P文
This is my husband, Kevin.
嗨!"老公"
Hi. "Husband."
- 我喜g@,新婚夫妻 - 恭禧
I like to say it. We are newlyweds.
Wow. Congratulations.
非常感x
Thank you so much.
我去了蜜月旅行
We went on a sweetheart honeymoon. Oh.
你去哪?
Where did you guys go?
- 迪士尼@ - 迪士尼@
Disney World. Disney World.
我一起v完最後一句,抱歉
We finish each ether's sentences. Sorry.
抱歉,@是先生?
Sorry. Is this your husband?
不…
No, no, no, no, no.
我不JR他,Σ黄
I don't know him. I'm sorry.
想散散步?
Do you want to go for a walk later?
不行喔
Oh. I can't.
- 好吧 - 我不行,抱歉
All right. I can't. I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我紊,唱角
I'm not with anybody. I'm here solo.
- 我再硪淮伟,我是卡 - 倒А
Let's start it again. I'm Becca. Rewind.
@是我先生,K]有老公
This is my husband. You don't have a husband.
又fe了
Sorry.
@位是小道的妹妹,梅根
And this is Dougie's sister, Megan.
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
我奶奶的酒杯好像空了,我R上就回
My grandma is not supposed to have wine. I'll be right back.
- 嘿 - 嘿,近砜珊?
Hey. Hey. How is it going?
好到不行,好到不行,在康椭
It's going great. It's going great. I'm on the mend.
我的腿打了赘
I just got some pins in my legs.
信不信由 我的腿上有,可以@犹
Believe it or not, pins in my legs, I can still do this. Right?
我倪[上下,但我活著
I fell off a cruise ship, but I'm back.
- 哇操 - ,"哇操"
Oh, shit. Yeah, "Oh, shit."
]e,"哇操"
Yeah, "Oh, shit."
重重摔下,O端落w,就像珠台
Took a hard, hard, violent fall. Kind of pin balled down.
Я诟,沿途摧
Hit a lot of railings, broke a lot of shit.
我不f@是幸存,而是更加茁
I'm not going to say I survived, I'm going to say I thrived.
我在水下遇到海豚
I met a dolphin down there.
我l誓那b海豚看到的不是我
And I swear to God, that dolphin looked not at me,
而是我的`魂
but into my soul.
直v我死的`魂,安妮
Into my goddamn soul, Annie.
f"我砭的,梅根"
And he said, "I'm saving you, Megan."
不是真的_口,但_f了 我想是心`感
Not with his mouth, but he said it, I'm assuming, telepathically
我怎N贤ㄎ乙膊缘谩神啊
We had a connection that I don't even know if I can... Jesus.
我]上嘴,看著… y以相信
Hey, shut my mouth. Look at... Unbelievable.
想必你是安妮的男人
You must be Annie's fella.
- 我是梅根 - 幸
I'm Megan. It's a pleasure.
他不是…我不是一
He's not... I'm not... He's not... I'm not with him.
抱歉
Sorry. All right.
好他紊,不然我把他成砼
I'm glad he's single, because I'm going to climb that like a tree.
一定要海
Okay. You have to meet Helen.
她就在那,海
There she is. Helen.
^戆!
Come here!
海,@位是安妮
Helen, this is Annie.
嗨
Hi! Ohh!
就是她啊,伴娘
There she is. Maid of honor.
到莉莉安的角之交真是有趣
So lovely to meet Lillian's childhood friend.
真漂亮
You are so pretty.
真是可!又甜美
You are so cute! You are so sweet.
海嫁o小道的老 哈里斯先生,派瑞
Helen is married to Dougie's boss, Mr. Harris. Perry.
派瑞,他F在粘的很
Perry. And they are so close now,
正_地f是Bw人
they are literally joined at the hip.
也好啦,因槲也是
Which is good, because so are we.
很_心算JR了
I know. I'm so glad you guys are finally meeting.
- Π,有同感 - 太好了
I know. Me, too. I know. it's lovely.
晌皇陪,我去巡一下小菜了
Well, excuse me, I better go check on the hors d'oeuvres.
- 但算能一H芳 - 派很成功
But it was great to finally meet you.
It's a great party.
- Enjoy. - Bye.
- M情享用 - 掰
- Bye. - Bye.
- 掰 - 掰
她很高F吧?
She's great, isn't she?
她很正c
She's awesome.
我引I期盼小道成槲家的一份子
And I really look forward to having Doug as part of our family.
恨不得扇笋R上Y婚
So much so that you two should get married right now
好省下大Pn票
and save me a shitload of money.
爸
Dad.
大家都一笑置之,但我不是f著玩
Everybody always laughs at that, but I'm not joking.
不是f著玩
I'm not joking.
好啦,我要感x您WR
Anyway, I want to thank all of you for coming.
e杯敬我的女,莉莉安
And here's to Doug and my baby girl, Lillian.
乾杯!乾杯!
Cheers! Cheers!
- 我,老爸 - 言至於此
- I love you, Dad. - Enough of me.
我g迎伴娘上台
Let's get the maid of honor up here.
- 安妮? - 好的
All right. Annie?
嗨,我是安妮渥克
Umm. Hi. I'm Annie Walker.
啦,安妮!
Yay, Annie!
我不打算高,就做短l言
I'm not going to go on with a big speech, so I'll just say this.
我很高d能⑴c喜宴
I'm so happy to be a part of this celebration.
而@μ煸]因
And you two deserve each other,
必能幸福LL久久
as well as a lifetime of happiness.
- 感x - 乾杯
- Thank you. - Cheers.
- 感x大家 - 乾杯
- Love you guys. - Cheers.
xx安妮,乾杯
Thanks, Annie. Cheers.
感x安妮,真是C心,xx
Thank you, Annie. That was so sweet. Thank you.
小莉,得和一群小夥子同[~阿密?
Lil, remember that trip we took to Miami with the boys?
他整L末都很忙
And they were working the entire weekend,
我就坐著喝酒,吃花生糖
and we just sat and drank wine and ate peanut brittle.
我跟分享我未曾f^的心事
And I shared things with you that I've never shared with anyone.
我再次w,是能信他人的
And you made me realize how I can trust people again.
所以允我@Nf
So let me just say,
莉莉安,是我最好的朋友
Lillian, you are my best friend.
我非常以s
And I'm so proud of you.
抱歉了,道格…
Sorry. And, Dougly...
我之g的玩笑
I'm sorry, inside joke.
你最好e把我的莉莉太o
You better not keep my Lil on a leash
因檫L末之夜需要有人陪我
because I still need my drunken Saturday nights
到uL鬯筹Π?
at Rockin' Sushi, okay?
大家e杯敬@κd佳偶
Everybody raise your glasses to the couple of the decade,
道格c莉莉安
Doug and Lillian.
大家M情享受吧,甜酒]了
Have a great night. Dessert wine is out.
甜酒好喝,不好意思
Dessert wine, yummy. Excuse me.
Umm...
我很快地f完
I just wanted to say really quick that
ξ叶言,真的很特e,因椤
you are so special to me, because...
我JR半子了
Well, one of the reasons is because I've known you my whole entire life.
塑造出今日的我
And you've really helped shape who I am.
我想要感x精心挑x
I just want to thank you for carefully selecting me
的伴娘
as your maid of honor.
我知道有其他人x
I know you had some other choices,
但就像姐妹掏,我
but you are like my sister, and I love you.
@就是今晚的Y
Well, that concludes the speeches for the night.
多x,最後一件事
Thank you. One last thing.
L大後要遇到投契的人真不容易
It's rare to meet someone as an adult who you really connect with,
就是,小莉
and that's you, Lil.
最近和我先生派瑞去泰
I went to Thailand recently with my husband, Perry,
我W到很美的一段
and there is a beautiful saying that I learned there.
意思是"我情同骨肉"
It means, "You are a part of me,
"缺了,我o以槔^"
"a part that I could never live without,
"我衷心祈\能永不分x"
"and I hope and I pray that I never have to."
@就是今晚的主旨,感xWR
And that's it for tonight. Thank you for coming.
- 很快就好 - 感x大家的WR
Really quick, Thank you all for coming.
- 我很快f完 - 最後一道甜c出完,姐妹掏
I just wanted to say really quick...
Dessert wine is out. Consuelo?
Really quick. Speaking of Consuelo,
很快就好,姐妹掏致o
Lillian and I took Spanish together in school.
莉莉安跟我一起修^西Z
因此,我想c各位f…
And so, I would just like to say to you, and to everyone here...
xx
Thank you.
xx,我X得很H切,又能信任
Thank you. I feel so close to you and can trust you.
是我的天使,莫逆之交
You are my angel and soul mate.
只要看一眼就能理解Ψ
And I feel I can communicate with you with simply a look.
xx光R
Thank you for coming.
,我拿就好,我拿就好
Here, I'll take that. I'll take that.
,我拿到了
Yep, I got it.
莉莉安
Lillian...
笑常_,面容常耀
Keep smiling, keep shining
表露我能常相偎S
Knowing you can always count on me
o庸置疑
For sure
@就是朋友之契
That's what friends are for
不管晴A缺
In good times and bad times
我永h永h支持
I'll be on your side forever more
That's what friends are for
- @就是朋友之契 - @就是朋友之契
啊,婚派T例
Man, engagement parties rule.
真是令我@奇
It made me feel awesome,
好像我可以再去客兄
like I can go out and catch another dude to marry.
是怎?跟海?
So, what's up with her, anyway? With Helen?
- 怎? - 好像…
What? I'm just like...
才JR8月吧?
I don't know. She's in your wedding
就要到的婚Y
and you've only known her eight months, though, right?
f吧,不吐不快
Come on. Get it out, get it all out.
我是f… 要穿全套Y服…之的
I'm just... Like, the whole gown, and the...thing.
- 很怪耶? - 知道?
It's just weird, right? You know what?
安妮,她本尊很H切
She's actually really cool, Annie.
她真的…是好人,就直f了
She's really... She's a good one. I'm telling you.
如果喜g她,那我也
Well, I'm sure if you like her, I will like her.
一定去JR她
You have to just get to know her.
- 好 - 我f真的
Yeah. Which I think you really should.
也臀忙?
And... Will you just do me a favor?
可以跟她一次?
Would you just hang out with her once,
just the two of you. All right?
As a favor to me.
就是在臀
我的
Okay, I will.
- 我,公妮 - 我也
I love you, Annie Lou. I love you, too.
- 掰 - 掰
Bye. Bye.
嗨!我是海
Oh. Hi, I'm Helen.
住密瓦基?真失Y
You live in Milwaukee? I'm sorry.
JR莉莉安?她是我的麻吉
Have you met Lillian? She's my best friend.
Π,後才JR5分
Yeah, I know. We've only known each other for five minutes.
喔!喔!
Oh! Oh!
喔!古F唷
on! Cute.
不吧
No. No. Come on.
看吧,就跟f我]醉
See? Okay? I'm not drunk. I told you.
那就是技g差?
So, you are just a terrible sober driver?
哈…好笑,可以停了?
Ha ha. Very funny. Can I stop walking now?
我叫停才能停
You can stop walking when I tell you to stop walking.
你看,要是我喝醉
Hey, look. If I was drunk,
我能@?
would I be able to do this?
e跳,e跳了,拜
Stop it. Stop it. Please, stop.
拜e跳,我信了,]喝醉
Please, stop. I believe you. You are not drunk.
但我是_P
But I'm still gonna have to give you a ticket.
啊?槭颤N?
What? why?
很奇怪,x一定有吧
It's a funny thing about brake lights. You have to have them.
天啊,我就知道,那已1年了
I knew it. God, those have been out for a year.
我太i^了
I'm so stupid.
拜
Look, please.
拜啦,我保C修好它
Please, I promise I will get them fixed.
@星期,我保C,非_t尾豢?
This week, I promise. Please. Do you have to give me a ticket?
,行照{照
Yes. License and registration, please.
xx
Thanks.
瞧瞧,住在孛魑迓
Look at that, you live on Wynnewood Drive.
-  - 我是居
Yep. We are neighbors.
我就住在艾胥那
I just live over on Ashley. Ahh.
我在艾胥工作^
I used to work on Ashley.
真的?在哪?
You did? Where?
我在那l街的[^_^一g烘焙店
I had a bakery on the main part of the street there.
甜在心西c
Oh. Cake Baby.
- 是老? -
You are Cake Baby! Yeah!
店面有招牌是的吧
Yeah, you had your sign. It was your face.
-  - 真的是?
Yeah! That was you?
就是我
That was me.
做的c心很|
You made good cakes.
多x
Thanks.
常做一些小糕c
You used to make these little pastry things,
在e面加奶油或是蛋奶
and you'd put something in them, like a cream or a custard...
奶油泡芙
Cream puffs.
奶油泡芙,就是的叫法,好吃
Cream puffs, that's what you call them. Delicious.
有一高高魁魁的人矸
I used to get served by this tall, broad guy,
像是月球表面
with, like, a wormy face.
,我的男友
Yeah, that was my boyfriend.
- 抱歉 - ]事,那是…
Sorry. No, no. It was...
曾是男友,後我
He was my boyfriend, and then he left me
就在生意一落千丈r
when the business went under. So, anyway...
不吧?
You're kidding?
夭酃!
What a dick.
幸好我]他的
I'm glad I never tipped him.
@影,就作]l生
You know what? Let's forget about this.
- 忘了@一次吧 - 真的?
Let's just forget this one. Really?
- 附l件 - 怎?
Under one condition. What? What?
去修好尾
Get your taillights fixed...
我答,]} 我答,感x你
I promise. I promise I will. I promise. Thank you.
在]害死人之前
...Before you kill someone.
我才不害死人
I'm not going to kill anybody.
拿去吧,的身份^
All right. Here, there's your ID.
我要o@
And I'm going to give you this.
我的夥伴,他在密瓦基_修S
It's a buddy of mine. He has a body shop in Milwaukee.
他修好
He'll fix those right up for you.
比寇仔?
Bill Cozbi?
,是"仔"
Yeah, with a "Z."
- c不同 -
Different guy. Yeah.
千fe在他面前提"比寇斯比"
And don't mention the whole "Bill Cosby" thing to him.
他抓狂,我是f真的
It drives him nuts. I mean it.
好,我懂了,xx
Okay, I get it. Thanks.
有啊,如果笪业拿字
You know what? If you mention my name, that I referred you,
他o特e折扣
he'll give you a particularly good deal.
天啊,xx你
My gosh. Thank you.
我真的很感激你,xx
I really appreciate it. Thanks.
我也感激的糕c
Okay. Well, I appreciated your cakes.
我扯平了
So, we are even.
@是我,_警官
That's me, there. Rhodes. Officer Rhodes.
你真是大好人
That's really nice of you.
感x你
Thank you.
警察不得都很
We are not all bad.
什N?
What?
- 我是f,警察不得都很! - 了解
I was just saying, we are not all bad!
Oh. Yeah.
其除了我都很
Actually, the rest of them are, but not me.
我是佼佼者
I'm the best of them.
了解,xx你
Okay. Thank you.
不哈啦了
Anyway.
xx你
Thank you.
我不知道有打W球
I didn't know you played tennis.
我高中有稍微打^
Yeah, I played a little in high school.
很高d我都
I'm so glad we were able to do this.
我也是,能跟出砭筒诲e了
I'm really glad we could do this, too. It's nice we get to hang out.
我了解
I know, right? Yeah.
可惜莉莉安不能泶
It's too bad Lillian couldn't play with us today.
小可z,她太忙了
Poor thing, she is so busy.
我知道
Ohh. I know.
但她\硬惶行
But she's not really that into sports.
就B小r候也都不
Even when we were little, she didn't like anything
\佣家你我Z
that was too competitive.
她F在真的很鄞蚓W球
She certainly enjoys playing tennis now.
人的改真有意思喔?
It's funny how people change, isn't it?
喔,不清楚,人真的?
Yeah. I mean, I don't know. Do people really change?
我想是的
I think they do.
但是本|是],很y改
Yeah, but, I mean, they still stay who they are, pretty much.
我想我Sr都在
I think we change all the time.
我X得是一,只是增L一些
I think we stay the same, but grow, I guess, a little bit.
我J樵鲩L就算是改了
I think if you are growing, then you are changing.
但是改是要谋举|,本性y移
But, I mean, we are changing from who we are, which we always stay as.
不得,我就不@N想
Not really, I don't think so.
- 我是@N想 - 我不同意
I think so. I don't.
安妮!@是我的小孩
Annie! These are my kids.
^子,"^"
Step-kids. Step.
他真是滑稽
They are so hilarious.
好笑
Funny.
抱歉,我先生的小孩
Excuse me, my husband's kids.
你要去哪?
What are you guys up to?
柑仔店
Going to the snack bar.
太棒了,要我d回家?
Awesome. You need a ride home later?
哭夭喔,海
Fuck off, Helen.
很好,P半角
Okay. Put a quarter in the swear-jar.
再
Good to see you.
真可
They are so cute.
一π】
Sweet kids.
P洛琳
Carol!
是不FYc喔,小P
Get your shit together, Carol!
啦!
Yes!
l生棉V告的W球好看多了
I've seen better tennis playing in a tampon commercial.
Umm...
我想^了
I've been thinking, and...
布恩要_始付房租了,就@
Brynn needs to start paying rent. That's it.
她也蚓昧
She's been here long enough.
@e有三人同住,我s要付一半很不公平
The three of us live here, it's not fair for me to be paying half.
我分三等份,意下如何?
We split it three ways. What do you say?
她o法工作,她持^光C
Well, she can't work. She's on a tourist visa.
,正_碚f,我只能^光
Yeah. So, technically, I'm only allowed to tour.
- 知道… - 我o法X
Well, you know...
I have no way of earning money,
除非我去站壁仔
unless I just go and prostitute down on the street.
- 我不想要@ - "哥,你好,我砹"
I don't want you to do that, no.
"Hello, fellas. Here I am."
Yeah, but we... "Put your American sausage
- 但是… - "把你的美u"
"插入我的英道"
"in my English McMuffin."
我不必@
No, we did that. All right.
我搞不懂你在f什N
Okay, I don't even know what you're talking about any more.
- @e有3人住 -
There's three people living here. Yeah.
- 如果她不出X - 我不出
If she doesn't start paying...
她就得x_
I'm not. ...she has to leave.
@是日的翻版?
Is this about the diary again?
什N日?
What diary?
的日真是非常有趣
Your diary proved very interesting to read.
看我的…日I?
You read my... You read my journal?
一_始我不知道那是的日
At first, I did not know that it was your diary.
以槭且槐臼分悲情的手抄
I thought it was a very sad, hand-written book.
- 什N? - 只是不太…
What? That does not make any...
- 但… - 因橛O殡[私的热
But, because of the deep personal details
- 提到吉c布恩 - 不行…
and the bits that mentioned Gil and Brynn... No, no, no, no.
- e看我的日I! - 到邋遢鬼
- Don't read my journal! - And the crumbs.
- 然後… - 不要M我的房g
Then... Don't go in my room!
嘿!我想在有所要求前
Well, hello! I think, before you make those sort of demands,
或S先要在T前Nlf
you need to, maybe, think about
putting a note on your door saying,
"eM我的房g看我的日,穿我的衣服"
"Do not come into my room, read my diary and wear my clothes."
我]磉^市^@N地方
Wow, I've never been to this part of town before.
隔壁有支票冬F的地方
Look, you can get your checks cashed next door.
店面看硪苍S人
I know it looks a little scary on the outside,
但食物肯定正c,可靠的巴西人
but the food is really good, authentic Brazilian.
我跟f,巴西人都磉@e吃
I'm telling you, this is where Brazilians come to eat.
我得f@安妮最擅L
I got to say, Annie's really good at this.
她常拉我去鬼地方
She always drags me to the weirdest places
但是有奇特的美食
and the food is always incredible.
有,可以大省荷包,一e傻
And plus, you get a lot for your money, too. So that's good.
那就M去用餐吧
All right. Let's do it. Let's do it.
!有人喜g巴西餐喔
Whoa! Somebody likes Brazilian food.
敬伴娘
To my bridesmaids.
- 乾杯 - 乾杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
樾±蚯!
Cheers to Lil!
真是一群s牌伴娘,我很傲
This is such a stone-cold pack of weirdos, and I'm so proud.
我想敬各位女士
And I just want to toast all of you ladies.
很_心JR
I'm so happy to get to know you guys,
可以YR4位新朋友
and happy to say that I have four new friends.
一c也]e,乾杯
Absolutely. Cheers.
安妮,有找到婚Y男伴?
So, Annie, do you have a date for the wedding?
Um...
我不…l都不想
I don't... I don't think I'm bringing anybody, I guess.
我_好了?拜啦?
Please, can I set you up? Please?
安妮,不能一人出席
Annie, you can't go to the wedding alone. Please?
要是为,人家以是妓女
If you go alone, people might think you're a prostitute.
可能喔
Maybe.
Σ黄
I'm sorry.
希望各位的胃b得下巴西烤,敬挑x?
I hope that you're all hungry for churrasco Brasil. What would you like?
我硪稽c@
Yeah, I'll have some of that, please.
我先吃@
I'll start with this.
碚卟痪,安否,u仔
I'd say yes. Hello, chicken.
大夥,真是好吃爆了
This is crazy good, ya'll.
海,我的肉o吧?
Helen, aren't you eating any meat?
b前我不鄞蟪源蠛
It's not good to eat a big meal before a fitting.
我有c,所以…
I feel a bit bloated, so...
我就不
Not me.
- 是喔? - 我K不感到胃
No? No. Physically, I don't bloat.
真幸福
Lucky. That is lucky.
@是天x
It's a gift.
看到Y婚,我也急著想完成Y婚的目的
I can't wait to be married for as long as you've been married.
生小孩
And to have kids.
,卡
And be a mom. Becca?
不e吧?
Yeah?
前滋斓耐砩,我忙到翻天
The other night, I'm slaving away,
弄好了S盛晚餐
making a beautiful dinner for my family.
我的么子跑M碚f他想披_
My youngest boy comes in and says he wants to order a pizza.
我f"不行,今晚不能"
I said, "No, we're not ordering pizza tonight."
他回",怎N不去吃大便?"
He goes, "Mom, why don't you go and fuck yourself?"
他才9q
He's nine.
好,乘莉莉安去洗手g
Okay, now that Lillian's in the bathroom,
我想一下出嫁送Y
I just wanted to talk to you guys about the shower really quick.
我打算法式主}
I was thinking it could be French-themed,
她@一生都想著去巴黎
since she's always wanted to go to Paris her whole life.
所以我想就加入巴黎元素
So I figured we could bring Paris here
喝香,吃法式c心
and have champagne and little cookies.
上面"莉莉安c道格"
They'd say "Lillian and Dougie" on them.
就泡在巧克力熔泉
We can dip them in chocolate fondue,
IK不e的起司
and get cheese from the nice part of the store.
- 我喜g - 好主意,安妮
I love that. Good idea, Annie.
l法式邀函,夥ㄊ斤L
We can have French invitations, the whole thing.
不X得@雍芎?
Don't you think that'd be nice?
太可哿!非常俏皮
That's adorable! That's really cute.
好拥
Good. Great.
我不知道,是很可
I don't know. It's really cute.
但我人J
But I feel like, personally, the Paris theme's
巴黎主}有c像在炫耀
a bit, "Been there, done that."
我X得可以再加
I just feel like we can top it.
再加一c意上去
We should throw some ideas around.
看看有]有想到其他主}
See if anyone else has a theme they had in mind
或者有不同的想法
or something they'd been thinking of.
皮克斯主}送Y?
What about a Pixar-themed shower?
我可挑喜g的角色硌b扮
And we all come dressed as our favorite Pixar character.
我想到更多了,Y俱凡
That, and I'll just snowball on top of that, also Fight Club.
女生版的
Female fight club.
T上油脂,全wnM
We grease up, we pull in.
在莉莉安不知情r 喊"@喜!我_打了!"
Lillian doesn't know, so it's, "Surprise! We're going to fight!"
然後把她打到挫屎
We beat the shit out of her.
^τ郎y忘
She's not going to forget that.
只要狠狠地攻
We just fucking attack.
- 我可以f真的? - 不行
Can I be honest? No.
我要和3小男生朝夕相
I'm at home with three boys all day, every day.
干脆就紊砼?
What about the bachelorette party?
@真的很重要
That's what's more important.
我I了一件小可,打算剪掉嘶`
I've got a new tube top, I want to cut the tags off.
正好可以藉由@次C
I'd like to take advantage of this opportunity.
- 要不要挑地c? - 我附和
Where are we going? I'm going to second her.
- 要就乘F在 -
We'd better blow this shit out. Yeah.
那小可z,莉莉安,今天的主角
That poor girl, Lillian, who we're all here for,
可能正在洗手g哭北哭目
is in the bathroom probably bawling her fucking eyes out.
因樗lF"鬼了!"
Because she's realizing, "Holy shit!
"我要跟小道要共渡N生"
"I've got to spend the rest of my life with Doug."
他是我哥哥,我鬯,但他是混蛋
He's my brother. I love him. But he is a fucking asshole.
我想大家都同意吧?
I think we can all agree on that, right?
到r候就知道了
We can... We'll figure it out.
我是f我再想k法,包君M意
I mean, I can think of stuff, and it will be great.
毡匾非常非常特e
We just have to make sure it's really, really special.
香法婚?髡f中的地方 值煤,安妮
Belle en Blanc? This is the place. Great job, Annie.
xx,安妮
Thanks. Annie.
香法婚,As大名?
Belle en Blanc. Reservation name?
我]有As,只是路^想碓穿
I don't have one. We're just here to shop, just to try on some dresses.
@余,伴娘b最快要等7L喔
Okay. Well, the next available appointment
for bridesmaids' fittings is in seven weeks.
Absolutely no walk-ins.
目前完全客M
惠妮?我是海
Whitney? It's Helen.
- 海哈里斯 -
Helen Harris? Yeah!
- 嗨 - 嗨
Hi! Hi.
天呀,我F在就_T
Oh, my God. Hi. Listen, I'll buzz you right in.
- 太好了,xx - 不
Great, thanks. Okay.
g迎,M
Hello. Welcome, come in.
真是雍容AF,太s幸了
You look wonderful. Great to see you.
g迎各位硐惴婚
Welcome to Belle en Blanc, ladies.
- g迎淼教焯 - xx
- Welcome to heaven. - Thank you.
啊
Oh, man!
真他的A
This is some classy shit here.
天啊,梅根
Jesus, Megan!
Σ黄,我道歉
I'm sorry, I want to apologize.
我也抓不rC啊
I'm not even confident on which end that came out of.
惠妮,Qv,Σ黄
Whitney, back to you. I'm sorry.
好啦,S便看看,JR一下Y服
Anyway, take a look around. Get to know the dresses.
有任何需要,我就在k公室
If you need anything, I'll be in my office.
好好看
Have fun.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
是菲姿伯人沟
It's a Fritz Bernaise.
小姐,我…天啊!
Ladies, I... Oh, my God!
我想]有更好的x窳,真是…
I just don't think we can do any better. This is...
真是美,太A了
This is beautiful. That is gorgeous.
一o二,很特e的女rb
It's unique, it's special, it's couture.
法u的
This is made in France.
海,@件800元
Helen, this is $800.
真的?在打折耶
Are you kidding? It's on sale.
- f真的? - 天啊,完美的M合
Are you serious? Oh, my gosh. What a perfect combination.
- 非不可 - 真不
You guys, it was meant to be.
Oh. that's nice.
There's other dresses we should be looking at.
我也⒖歼@准的
@件不算
Nope, not that one.
莉莉安,看@件
Lillian, Lillian, look at this one.
- 很漂亮吧? -
Isn't this pretty? Yeah.
非常的漂亮,很喜
It's really pretty and sweet, and...
又不走莉莉安的光采
We don't want to upstage Lillian with a big fancy dress.
也S我是保持闼匦
Maybe we should just get something kind of simple.
Oh.
e心走我的焦c
Please do not worry about upstaging me.
因,猜海哪位朋友臀以O婚?
Because guess who Helen is friends with
and who's designing my wedding dress.
Lady St. Petsois JuJu.
}佩莎娃幸巫
- 我把我的尺寸送到巴黎了 - 不吧
I just sent my measurements to France, y'all.
No, you didn't.
Where were you when I was getting married?
我Y婚的r候人在哪?
女士,我不用F在就Q定Y服
Ladies, let's not decide on this bridesmaids' dress straight away.
只有身材的}
Let's let our bodies decide.
就穿好玩的吧?
Try some things on and have some fun, okay?
- Π,M情享受吧,小姐 - 女士,l右擎
Yeah, let's have some fun, girls.
Ladies, start your "engines."
- Oh, yeah. - Lil, Lil.
小莉,小莉
- 太美了 - 真是蜢诺
- Amazing. - This is so cool.
女士,允S我插
Ladies. Ladies, if I may interject.
我想f,真是迷人
I just want to say you all look stunning.
天生衣架子,念^到_
That's a given. Head to toe.
可惜的是,我只能挑一套
But, sadly, we need to agree on one.
我想都非常美
Well, I mean, ladies, you all look beautiful.
但我人J,菲姿伯{斯真的是…
But I just think, personally, the Fritz Bernaise is just...
@是伯{斯的
I mean... it's a Bernaise.
就只有@N一款可挑
This is one of a kind. I just...
我想}K不大
I don't think there is a question.
,]}
No. No question.
可能有}
There might be a question.
我可能就有}
I might... I might have a question.
我X得@套大家都很m合
I think this dress would look great on everybody.
色{出色,剪裁完美
It's a great color. It's a great length.
很有趣,可以甩裙
It's fun. You can twirl.
可以塞手
You can move in it.
可以赡___
You can spread your legs apart.
而且r格惠
And it's a great price.
也是出自O之手
This is designer as well.
有人X得?
Is anyone else hot?
@e好像烤箱
It is like an oven in here.
也S@有助各位的Q定
Okay, well, maybe this might help you decide.
在更衣室r
While you gals were in the changing room,
我囊谎e翻出有2年的幸巫大作
I happened to rustle up a two-year-old Lady JuJu dress in storage.
我莉莉安穿上
I had Lillian put it on so you could see
o各位先R一下
what you'll be standing next to.
H鄣睦蚶虬
Lillian, honey.
天啊
My God.
漂亮的裙尾
Beautiful length.
太吸晴了
Breathtaking.
哇塞!真是美呆了
Holy shit! You look amazing.
@件真是太美了
That's a dress. That dress is so pretty
美到我胃痛
it makes my stomach hurt.
莉莉安
Lillian,
我不知如何形容,真是…
- I don't know what to say. - You look...
梅根,]事吧?
Megan, are you okay?
我X得…
I think...
可能是Y服太o了
My dress was probably just tight.
天啊
Oh, my God.
是在餐d吃亩亲影?
You got food poisoning from that restaurant, didn't you?
不可能,我跟她吃的一,我就]事
No, I had the same thing that she had and I feel fine.
天…好吧
Oh, my... Okay. Oh, no.
- 怎N@? - ]怎N
Why is this happening? Nothing is happening.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我才不管我穿什N
I don't really care which dress we get.
那不重要,但我得x_@K白地毯
It doesn't matter to me. I just need to get off this white carpet.
,只能在洗手g
Oh, God. Okay. No, not the bathroom.
大家快出去,我是f真的!
Everybody go outside. I'm serious!
γ嬗幸婚g洗手g
There is a bathroom across the street.
我想大家得了流感
I think everybody has the flu.
R的!
Shit!
我要R桶!我要R桶!
I need the toilet! I need the toilet!
我要R桶!
I need the toilet!
不!
No!
不,梅根,不!
No. No, Megan. No! No!
- D^^去 - 梅根,不!
Look away! Megan, no!
D^^去!
Look away!
馍不佳喔,安妮
You don't look very well, Annie.
我]事
I feel fine.
真的?不是死白色的羊肉吧?
Are you sure? It wasn't that gray kind of lamb?
你吃了不少的怪u肉
You ate a lot of that weird chicken.
是那?
Was it that?
不是,我…
No. I'm...
我X得很好
I... I feel fine.
我X得去吐一吐比^舒服
I think you'd just feel better if you threw up.
我不必…]有必要吐
I don't have... I don't have to throw up.
非常抱歉
I am so sorry.
o我L_!
Get away from me!
]病吧?
You're not sick?
-  - 真的?
No. No?
f真的,海,我有cI
In fact, Helen, I'm hungry.
真希望有c心吃
And I wish I had a snack.
I了?
You're hungry?
超I的
I'm starving.
我吃了什N?
What did we eat?
- 洗水台]救了 - 在致?
The sink is a goner. What are you doing?
就像火山爆l!
It's coming out of me like lava!
天啊
Oh, my God.
致锒⒅我看!
Don't you fucking look at me!
Hmm?
s旦杏仁
Jordan almonds.
真是高
These are great.
多x了
Thank you.
好c]?
Better?
- 真的I到 - 是哦
I was... I was just hungry.
Yeah.
安妮,大家都在餐d吃亩亲恿
Annie, everybody is really sick from that restaurant.
- 但}不是出在餐d - 不行了
But it wasn't the restaurant. No, no, no, no.
莉莉安,去哪
Lillian, where are you going? No.
上所
I need a bathroom.
小莉!
Lil!
不…
No. No.
小莉,去哪?
Lil, where are you going?
小心,在致?
Be careful. What are you doing?
出砹,出砹,出砹
It's happening. It's happening.
- 出去了 - 在致?
- It happened. - What are you doing?
出去了
It happened.
e想Я硕Y服!
No. Don't you dare ruin that dress!
不是碚娴陌?
Ohh. You're really doing it, aren't you?
真的拉在R路上了
You're really shitting in the street.
我Q定拿5套菲姿伯{斯
We'll just take five of the Fritz Bernaises.
xx,惠妮,真的非常好看
Thank you, Whitney. They really do look better.
好,xx
Right. Thank you.
]事吧?
You okay?
我拉在我的Y服,我拉…
I crapped my wedding dress. I crapped...
我拉在我的Y服
I... I crapped my wedding dress.
不^午餐很有趣Π?
Lunch was fun, though, right?
幸福r光,大家聚在一K
It was a good time, all the girls together.
@是凶兆,安妮?
Is this a sign, Annie?
不是,我路停一下,因椤
No. I'm just going to pull over
really quick, though, because...
What?
怎?
...My tire just feels a little...
我的胎好像有c…
Where are you going?
要去哪?
My tire just feels a little low.
我的胎好像有c]
I just want to check my tire real quick.
我去z查一下胎
可以跟借剃刀,拜?
Oh. Could I borrow your razor, please?
xx
Thank you. Mmm-hmm.
- s愉快 - xx
Have a good date. Thank you.
那人也是40q以上?
Is the guy that you're going out with also over 40?
我]40,算了
I'm not over 40. Forget it.
e起手臂,往上
Lift up your arm. Point up.
- 哦! - 抱歉
Ow! Sorry.
嗨,安妮
Hi. Annie.
- 小彼! -
Pete? Yeah.
M
Come on in.
好,xx
All right. Thank you.
@是我鹤,泰勒
Oh. This is my son, Tyler.
- 嗨,泰勒 - 嗨
Hi, Tyler. Hi.
- @n事是另人t - Π
These things are always so awkward. Yeah.
- 我不是一位S便的人 - 我也是
I'm not really a setup guy. Me, either.
但卡一直在v
But Becca spoke so highly of you.
她也大肆形容你的c
She had a lot of really nice things to say about you, too.
真是中
That's nice to hear.
我要去巧显俣啻准
I'm going to go upstairs, throw on a couple of finishing touches.
褓姆],所以就跟泰勒一下
The babysitter's not here yet, so just hang out with Tyler
- 我等一回就下 - 好
and I'll be right back down. Okay.
好
Okay.
你q?
So, how old are you?
看影?
Do you watch movies?
敢面λ劳?
Are you afraid of dying?
嗯?
Hmm?
敢面λ劳?
Are you afraid of dying?
Um...
不知道
I don't know.
我想大家都吧,不清楚,怎Nf?
I mean, I guess everybody is. I don't know. Why?
因槲打算
Because my mom is going to kill you.
我很不舒服
You're making me uncomfortable.
的^好像被^
Your hair looks burned.
好吧
Okay.
要跟我爸爸生小孩?
Are you going to make a baby with my father?
我不清楚
I don't... I don't know.
我奶奶死在坐的位置
My grandma died where you're sitting.
她在@e^逝?
She died right here?
就在的妊下
Right where your underpants are.
想看我跳舞?
You wanna watch me dance?
好啊
Sure.
我k不到
I can't do this.
我f,我非常想
Listen to me. I miss you so much.
我R上就要面α
I'll come over right now.
PI是我不能
Okay, I'm not over you yet, that's why.
她甚至不上
She's not even pretty.
我不要去做,k不到
I'm not doing it. I can't. No.
你在做什N?你有吃了?
What are you doing? Did you eat one of those?
你有吃其中一w?
Did you eat one of those?
我星期六吃
I ate Saturday.
乖,知道
Okay. Oh, boy. You know what?
你_始有反,我不知道怎N
Something's going to happen to you. I don't know what it is,
但你的身w_始怪怪的
but something's going to happen to your body.
- 太爽了 - 我的天啊
That was fun. Oh, my gosh.
你知道我怎N想?
You know what I was thinking?
你跟我一同出席莉莉安的婚Y
You should come with me to Lillian's wedding, maybe.
不用正八百的
Not like that. Not like anything serious.
就只是渭好玩
But just like a fun time, you know?
我可以穿Y服,跳跳舞,小喝一杯
We can get dressed up, and we can go dancing and have a drink.
很有趣Π?
It'll be fun, right?
不知道,我不想逢人就解
No. I mean, I don't want to make you have to explain
我的PS
to all those people what our relationship is.
灰^土Π?
That would suck for you. Right?
,我想是吧
Yeah. I guess so.
- 我是著想 - 好
I'm just thinking of you. Yeah.
]PS
No, it's okay.
反正我有一人x,所以…
I have someone else I can ask, anyway. So...
- 真的? -
Really? Yeah.
l?
Who?
@人叫讨
Umm... This guy, George.
讨胃鹄账
George Glass.
好吧
Okay.
他是何方神}?
Who is this George?
他非常惹火,大好人
He is a very hot, nice guy
非常喜g我,也可能芬猱我的男伴
who likes me a lot, and would probably love to be my date.
真的?
Really? Mmm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
那我
Well, let me ask you this.
讨胃鹄账用@招
Can this George Glass
do this to you?
可能喔
Probably.
知道?r候真的不早了
You know what? It's getting really late.
是x_了,我非常想的
You should probably go. I'm going to miss you so much.
Oh.
安妮渥克
Annie Walker.
嗨
Hi.
- 嘿 - 嘿
Hey. Hey.
是什NL一早就把吹?
What brings you in here so early?
才渡^黑色之夜,一小伙子
I've just had a bad night. Boy stuff. Ohh.
要我出R逮人?
Do you want me to arrest anybody?
我可以喔
I could do that.
其…不用
Actually... No.
想跟l子吐苦水?我就像神父
Do you want to talk to a cop about it? We are just like priests.
只差下後可以跟e人f
Except we can tell everybody about it after wards.
不^我不
Oh. I won't, though.
T因不足
Doesn't sound very inviting.
要不要吃}N?
You want a carrot?
- F在? -
Right now? Yeah.
分你吃,我有一大包
I'll share. I've got plenty.
- 好啊,那就不客饬 - 真的?
Sure, I'll have a carrot.
戆?
Yeah?
好吧
Okay.
好像很陋
Ohh. Yeah, that sounds rough.
好D吧?
It's going to get better, right?
我可不@N想
I wouldn't have thought so.
我妹妹^表H家的伴娘
You know, my sister was a maid of honor at our cousin's wedding,
她倍感毫,不停掉
and she found it so stressful, her hair started falling out.
- 好K喔 - Π
That's terrible. Yeah.
是L回砹,但是…
It grew back, but it was...
是M乐氐
It was pretty gross.
I婚Y很好玩
Planning a wedding should be fun.
如果啊,我要Y婚
You know what? If I ever had a wedding,
我客人S意穿
I'd want everybody to be stress-free.
婚Y像黾文耆A
I'd like it to be like a carnival.
猜新娘w重得大
Like, people win prizes for guessing the bride's weight.
落水[
Dunk tanks.
- 不e - 了解吧?
Yeah. You know?
你可以找大象
Mmm-hmm. You could have elephants,
新娘新郎可以走z
and the bride and groom can walk on a little tightrope.
v的是RF婚Y
Okay, what you are talking about there, that's a circus wedding.
- 完全不同 - 喔
It's a totally different... Right.
- `了 -
You missed it. Yeah.
除了要@龌槎Y
Hey, you know, instead of stressing out about this wedding,
起一件事
you know what you should be doing?
_新的烘焙坊!
Setting up a new bakery!
Hmm.
不了,我死心了
No, I'm kind of done with that.
不吧?
What?
我不再_店了
I don't do it any more.
好吧
All right.
Ew. Oh!
- 拿到畸形}N - 什N?
You got the ugly carrot. What?
一包只有一 要吃下去,砗眠\
There is one in every bag. You have to eat it. It's good luck.
我才不吃哩
I'm not eating this.
快!那我要吃了
Yeah! I'll eat it.
@是幸\}N? 不要,不要吃啦!
It's the lucky carrot? No, don't eat it! Don't eat it. Don't eat it!
- 不能S意yG!我P喔 - Σ黄
Well, don't litter! I'll fine you. I'm sorry.
告V,我要把它炱
You know what? Actually, I'm going to pick it up.
- @游曳浅＠_ - 抱歉
It really bothers me. Sorry.
Σ黄,@像我拉出淼
I'm sorry. It's just that I'm anal about that kind of thing.
我不知道你穿制服r 能跟我@幼著聊
I didn't know that you could be a cop here if you weren't a citizen.
- 是不行 - 真的?
You can't. No?
,不行
No. No, you can't.
上^他_了G
But they made a special dispensation
因槲,
because I'm so tough and strong.
而且很
Oh. Right. And handsome.
了解
Okay.
你非常悍
You're pretty... You're pretty tough.
- 我很悍 - 你是悍的l子
I am tough. You're tough. You're a tough cop.
f完笑
Look. You're saying it, but you're laughing.
]有,是…
No, you're... You're...
你]有我o肌肉
You didn't let me flex that time.
不公平,我是真的很猛
That was unfair. I'm really tough.
- 我也是 - 不可能
So am I. No.
我可以女警
Yeah. I could be a cop.
- J可以警察 - Π
You think you could be a cop? Yeah.
- 好啊 -
Okay. Yeah.
我想想,@影
Let's see. You know what?
太就快出,我就的能耐
The sun is nearly up. Let's go and see if you've got what it takes.
- ]e,F在站的_ - 好了
That's right. Now, plant your feet.
Okay.
很好
Good.
然後瞄
And take aim.
F在把的手放到X後
Now, put your left hand behind your head.
,然後重心放在左臀
Yeah. And just drop your left hip.
- _玩笑的,p臂保持平直 - 好
I'm kidding. Put your arms out straight. Okay.
受牌中g
You want to hit the middle of the license plate.
@ex到的值最正_
That's where you get the most accurate reading.
,就是@,好了?
Okay. Okay, here we go. You ready?
好了
Okay.
58,超速是多少?
Fifty-eight. What's the speed limit?
Fifty-five.
@]PS,我放^他
Okay, they were all right. We'll let them go.
天生警察的料,看看
You were born to do this. Look at you.
好啦,又有了
Okay. All right, here we go.
Sixty-three.
你放^一l大~了
You are missing some good ones here.
他s著上班,何必Я巳思?
People are on their way to work. Why ruin their day?
看好,48
Okay, watch this. 48.
48,你怎Nk到的?
Forty-eight. How did you do that?
- ]^! - 一定有
It wasn't! Yes, it was.
- ]猜^ - 你f真的?
That's never happened. Are you serious?
- 是48? - ,48!
It was 48? Yes, 48!
另我刮目相看
Yeah. I'm so impressed.
我也印象深刻
I'm pretty impressive.
我才δ懔硌巯啻
I'm very impressed by you.
Whoa!
死
Whoa! Damn!
- r速91哩 - 91?
That was 91. 91?
- 很好 - 可以抓?
Yes. Can we go?
可以抓了
We can go.
上,神警
Come on, hot dogger.
去抓那j仔吧
Let's get that fucker.
我的天啊!
ANNIE; on, my God!
Oh, my God!
"我想到莉莉安的紊砼σ去哪了"
...Family lake house. Perfect.
家族的湖畔小屋,完美
- 哈? - 我收到的e-mail,去湖畔小屋?
Hello? I just got your e-mail. Lake house?
Π
Yeah.
莉莉安pH的家
Yeah, it's Lillian's parents' house.
我常常夏天的r候去
We used to go there all the time in the summers and everything.
在小木屋ek趴?
It's one oi.. A bachelorette in a cabin?
等等,可以等一下
Wait. Can you..4 Hold that thought. Hold on.
哈?
Hello?
去的海,哈?
Fucking Helen. Hello?
安妮,我是塔
Annie, it's Rita.
嗨
Hi.
著,我想要能永生y忘的旅程
Listen, I need a trip that I can fantasize forever
好我能跟我先生
so that I am able to have sex with my husband.
所以我才想去城的
That's why I'm thinking Vegas.
城?
Vegas?
等一回,嘿!
Hang on. Hey!
]上你那v嘴巴!Σ黄
Shut your filth y fucking mouths! I'm sorry.
我被一群U人包
I'm surrounded by savages.
我炝,有黼插播
You know what? I should probably run. My other line is ringing.
我可以奈业睦眢d拿到古柯|
You know, I can get cocaine from my hairdresser.
- 掰 - 哈?
Okay, bye. Hello?
- 安妮 -
Annie. Yeah?
我非常d^,海f我可以去城
I'm so excited. Helen just called. She said we can go to Vegas.
知道,只是要…要w到那
You know... Yeah, but we have to... We have to fly there, and...
安妮,我知道怕搭wC
Okay, Annie, I know you are afraid of flying,
但我想去看克里斯安吉,也是既
but I want to see Criss Angel, but I'm scared.
又怕受害
Which I sort of love.
方便等我一下?
Can you just hold on for one second?
- 然了 - x了,等等,死
Oh, sure, sure, sure. I... Thanks. Hold on. God damn it.
- 哈? - 安妮,我是梅根
Hello? Hey, Annie, it's Megan.
嘿
Hey.
P於紊砼课矣悬c想法
I just had some thoughts about the bachelorette party.
好,我f了
Okay, here we go.
一句,就是城
Easy-peasy. Vegas it is.
海打oΠ?
Helen called you, didn't she?
,她早一步
Yeah, she got the jump on you.
我想含F蛋
I want balls in my face.
真心,就是城
Honestly, I think it's Vegas.
- 我想看傀儡 - 老二
I love puppets. Balls.
我是]有定案
I guess we are undecided.
安妮被G在我很^意不去
I feel so bad Annie's stuck back in coach.
我想退付,她可以坐^等
I know, I offered to pay for her
so she could sit in first class,
但她拒^
but she said no.
太高傲了
She's too proud.
的e雍苜N心
It was nice of you to offer.
空手搭C啊?
No carry-on, huh?
-  - 我注意到了
No. Yeah, I noticed.
我也注意到您]用^置物
I noticed you didn't put anything in the overhead bin either.
我就懂了
And I get it.
我懂了,我希望您知道-守o安全
I get it. I want you to know, protect and serve
空中警L
Air Marshal-style.
什N?
What?
我不想侵犯您的[私
I don't want to infringe on your privacy, man.
我只是很感激您家的奉I
I just... I really appreciate what you do for this country.
打男难e尊敬您
And I respect the hell out of you.
太好了
That's great.
我不是空中警L,我要[一下
I'm not an Air Marshal. I'm going to take a nap.
- 正c - 很好
Awesome. Cool.
我湍先期刹
I'll take the first watch.
我不是空中警L,不需要刹
I'm not an Air Marshal. You don't need to take a watch.
好了
Okay.
我做完F地刹炝
I've got the first watch.
"z查您的安全"
Please check your seat belts
"起w前,座位保持直立"
and that your seat backs are in an upright position before takeoff
天啊
Gosh.
真希望能w快c
I am really hoping this flight is quick,
平安降落
and we get there on the ground safely.
我不擅搭C,抱歉
I'm not a good flyer, I'm sorry.
我昨天舻轿C
I had a dream last night that we went down.
是很糟,也在e面
Yep. It was terrible. You were in it.
- 什N? - 好像有事情要l生了
What? It sounds like something's happening.
安妮,磉@e做什N?
Annie, what are you doing up here?
- 在的座位上 - 我知道,我有c牧
You are supposed to be in your seat.
I know. I'm freaking out a little bit.
女士,我在起w,要回去的座位
Ma'am, we're still ascending. You're gonna need to return to your seat.
好,我只是…
Okay, I was just...
安妮,我Я诉@
Annie, I have something.
服2w,就昏睡,醒磲峋偷搅
Take two, you'll fall asleep, wake up and we'll be there. Here.
女士,R上回去的座位
Ma'am, you're going to have to return to your seat, please.
- ]事的 - 好吧
It's fine. Okay. All right.
- 女士! - 叫屁喔
- Ma'am! - All right. All right.
天啊,真愧疚,我跟她坐的
Oh, my God, I feel terrible, I should be sitting back there with her.
我不坐到^等,我真是混蛋
I shouldn't be up here in first class. I feel like such a jerk.
小莉,@L末是凫的
Lil, this is your weekend, okay?
要,放p
You are treating yourself. Just relax.
她]事的,她交到新朋友
She will be fine. She will make friends.
那e更m合交友
There is much more sense of community in coach, I promise you.
我向保^,她]事的
She'll be fine.
我不相信奈锤e的人有^
I can't believe you've never been with anybody else.
只有P文
Just Kevin.
Σ黄,我只是…
I'm sorry. I just...
卡,我忍不住要感到悲哀
Becca, I just can't help but feel bad for you.
甚至不t解的需求
You don't even know what you want.
我要知道你把藏在哪
I got to know where you keep the gun, man.
_踝,屁股,後腰?
I mean, is it ankle, hip, lower back?
是藏在善ㄖg?
You don't... Between the cheeks, do you?
我才不把黏在屁股e,那太蠢了
No, I don't stick a gun up my butt. That's stupid.
我]f"e"喔
I didn't say "up."
我JR一L期P底的人
I just knew of a guy, that guy did a lot of undercover work.
他在屁股gNMz
And all I know is he had tape marks all up and down his cheeks.
行不通的
That can't be true.
哪有人把塞在屁股的
People don't keep guns up their asses
如果你想用的r候要怎N拿?
because if you needed to use it, how are you going to get it?
他在口袋切出一洞
He cut a hole in his pocket.
啥咪?在他後面的口袋
What? In his back pocket.
你得在子後面切一洞
You have got to get something out of your ass
才能取出砘
and you cut a hole in the back of your jeans,
你是想f你o法藏|西吧?
you want to tell me you can't get to something?
我是]有碜C明塞屁股的c
I don't have a gun for you to put up my ass to make your point.
我可以放Nano,我C明o你看
I can put my Nano. I will show you.
如果你有剪刀
I will... If you get me scissors,
我就可以在口袋剪洞
I will cut a hole in my pocket.
你就永h找不到了,除非我你搜
And you will never find this again until I want you to find it.
P文只能在床上,P,w棉被才能炒
Kevin can only have sex in bed, in the dark, under the covers,
要都洗完澡
only after we have showered
分_洗
separately.
有r候,我都洗完澡r
And sometimes, by the time we are finished
他累了
cleaning ourselves, he's too tired.
我要假b我很累,我很累
And then I pretend I'm tired, but I'm not tired. I'm not tired. I'm not tired.
所以女生都想在大W期g荒淫o度
That's why every girl needs those slutty college years.
w身w的O限,找到自己的口味
To experiment, get it out of your system, find out what you like.
,方便的臀业贡酒
Excuse me, could I have a glass of alcohol when you get a chance?
2杯p份7威7喜
Two double Seven and Sevens.
那是…
Is that...
喜g的,很口
You will like it. It's sweet.
我想上所
I have to go to the bathroom.
但我f有女的在C上如r
But I heard about a woman who went to the bathroom on a plane.
被吸到R桶e去
She got sucked into the toilet.
直接被吸入
Sucked right in.
好吧?
Are you okay?
]事
Yes.
我X得o的]什N作用
Yeah, I just think that what you gave me didn't really do anything.
我的I上腺素j太高了,多x了
I just have too much adrenalin or something. But, thanks.
要不要我的威士忌?
Why don't you take my scotch?
它丸更快作用
It will just give the pill a little kick that it needs.
- 坦白f,我都是@幼 - 喔?
Honestly, I do it all the time. Yeah?
,我酒量比小,不醉的
Yeah, and I'm much smaller than you, so you'll handle it.
多x了
Well, thanks.
那就好
Yeah? Okay.
好喝?
Yummy?
不e
Yeah, it's good.
- 一口喝光,e再等了 - 好
You should just toss it back. Don't waste any more time.
Okay.
@就α
Ohh. LOOK at that.
s快作用
Okay, that'll do it. That'll do it.
所以就]再做哿?
So you don't even have sex any more?
有,我很常做
No, I have sex constantly.
]有停^
The sex is constant.
但他有5年]H^我
But he hasn't kissed me in five years.
做鄣r候都在致?
What are you doing when you are having sex, then?
想e的事,希望草草Y束
Thinking about other things and wishing it would stop.
有r候他]插我r
You know, sometimes I just want to watch
我就D到每日新
The Daily Show without him entering me.
- 有比基尼@ - 不吧
It's the Wet Republic Ultra Pool. No.
怎N可能?
Are you kidding?
又砹?
What is it again?
泳池中有一酒吧,有老虎
There is a bar in the pool and a tiger.
什N?
What?
- 太狂了 - @是城之最
- it's crazy. - It's Vegas at its best.
等一下,真世界就是在@取景的?
Wait a minute. Is this that place that was on The Real World?
真的假的?天啊
Are you kidding me? Oh, my God. It's...
麻吉,舒服c]?
Hey, buddy. How you doing?
很好,通w舒 多x了,海
I'm good. I'm so much more relaxed. Thank you, Helen.
X得d^,很放
I just feel like I'm excited, and I feel relaxed.
我浜靡
And I'm ready
_趴了
to party
c^佳的夥伴
with the best of them!
我即㈨河水而下
And i'm going to go down to the river
好像有人^^
Wow! It looks like somebody is really relaxing now.
在@e聊什N?
What are you guys talking about up here?
我今天要去的餐d,我JRI主
We are going to a restaurant tonight. I know the owner, so...
是喔?
You do?
海JRI主
Ohh. Helen knows the owner.
Uhh!
Big whoop.
我去小睡一下好?
Let's go take a nap. What do you say?
小姐,不能上磉@e
Miss, you cannot be up here.
哈,阿桑
Hello, grandpa.
抱歉,我只想砼阄业呐笥
I'm sorry. I just want to be here with
因槲是Fw
my friends, because I'm with this group.
籼]亮了,能不能她聊一下
The sign just went off. Can't she stay up here for a minute and just talk?
^Σ恍
Absolutely not.
乘客不允S上眍^等
Coach passengers are not allowed up here in first class.
@是定,很抱歉
It's policy. I'm sorry.
Ooh!
我搭上的班C令森
This is a very strict plane that I'm on.
g迎淼降乱庵
Welcome to Germany.
再,混蛋
Auf Wiedersehen, asshole.
好了吧
All right.
就去躺著休息吧
Why don't you go lay down?
我要去打盹,我累了
I'm going to go take a nap. I'm tired.
好主意
I think it's a good idea.
下C後要你好看,s羚羊
Catch you on the flip side, motherfuckers.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我走了
I'm leaving.
感x
Thank you.
@要打_的,公民!
This should be open, because it's civil rights.
F在是90年代
This is the '90s.
K不是,的年代不
Right. It's not. You're in the wrong decade.
- 你啦 -
You are. Okay, I am.
xx
Thank you.
哇操,o她嗑什N?
Holy shit. What did you give her?
小姐?
Miss?
那不是我
No. it's not me.
就是,回到的座位
Yes, it is you. Please go back to your seat.
@e就是了
Yes, I am with him.
我是安立奎的太太
I am Mrs. Iglesias.
K不是
No, you are not.
只是戴太眼R而已,x_
You were just out here and you put sunglasses on. Out.
但我不想
But I don't want to.
先生,她可以坐我的位子
Sir, she can have my seat, okay?
人生都w一下^等
Everyone should experience first class at least once in their lives.
安妮不因楦恫黄鹁湾e失C
And Annie shouldn't miss out just because she can't afford it.
不行,女士,恐怕行不通
No, ma'am, I'm afraid that's not allowed.
- 救我@F人 - 著
- Help me, I'm poor. - No, listen,
我都要去派,我是新娘,浣Y婚了
we're a whole wedding party. I'm the bride. I'm getting married.
@位置是空的,她@然很o 我要安帷
This seat is empty. She's obviously nervous. We'll calm her down and...
我明白,但克裂f的
I understand. But Claire is right.
大家回各自的座位
Everybody, go back to your seats.
尤其是
Okay, you especially.
我o3秒回到的座位
You have three seconds to get back to your seat.
3秒哪都去不了
You can't get anywhere in three seconds.
但最好eFX
Well, you'd better try.
你我陷入困境
You are setting me up for a loss already.
xx
Thank you.
你f的算,火t
Whatever YOU Say, Stove.
是w柔
It's Steve.
"火t",怎N有@N名字?
"Stove." What kind of name is that?
那不是我的名字,我叫w柔
That's not a name. My name is Steve.
你是家?
Are you an appliance?
不,我是人,叫w柔
No, I'm a man, and my name is Steve.
你是空服T
You are a flight attendant.
正_o`
That's absolutely accurate.
可以拉起砹,xx
You can close that. Thank you.
"非"空中警L,
Hey, not-Air Marshall Jon.
你想男菹⑹一厝ザ不休息?
You want to get back in that restroom and not rest?
]有,我要回去我的位子
No, I have to get back to my seat.
那你得回我到我的位子
Yeah, you gotta get back on my seat.
懂?
You get it?
我完全明白
Yeah, I definitely got it.
@是什N?
Oh-Oh. what's That?
我要回去座位了,可以移的_?
I got to get back to my seat. Could you just move your leg, please?
我要走了
I got to go.
Oh-oh. Oh-oh.
某人找到o念品了
Somebody found a souvenir.
有感受到我底P的蒸汽?
You feel that steam heat coming? That's from my undercarriage
可以更高喔
That can go up and higher.
好了
Okay.
- ,臀拿毛毯 - 不要
Jon, get us a blanket.
No.
我uu完就回去了
I got to take a whiz and I'll be right back.
酷
Cool.
我不希望跟我一K
I don't want you to be a big fuck-up like me.
怎N懂我的感受?
How do you think I feel?
就像我,是能回^再
Like me. You can still turn it around.
e@
No, don't.
e[了!
Stop it!
比灰姑娘要正
You are more beautiful than Cinderella.
有松香,光的蛋
You smell like pine needles and you have a face like sunshine.
不吧?
What?
不
Oh, no.
先生女士
Ladies and gentlemen,
各位看到CL_"M安全"的
as you can see, the captain has turned on the ”fasten seat belt” sign.
@示我M入不定的夂
It appears we've run into a rough patch of weather...
我也有明
I have an announcement, too.
C翼上有名殖民D女
There is a Colonial woman on the wing.
C翼上有名殖民D女,我看到她
There's a woman on the wing. I saw her.
他有事m著我
There 's something they're not telling us!
- w柔 - 好的
Steve. All right.
有殖民D女
There's a Colonial woman.
- 她在C翼上打奶油 - w柔,抓住她
She was churning butter on that wing. Steve, get her.
- 她x_那了 - R的!
She is out there right now. Shit!
大家保持忍o,我是空中警L
Everyone, remain calm! I'm an Air Marshal.
!我就知道 我跟上去了,!
Yes! I knew it. I got your back, Jon!
C翼上有名D女,我看到她
There is a woman on the wing. I saw her.
他有事m著我
There's something they're not telling us.
快出去!快打_T逃出去吧!
Let's get out! Let's open the doors and get out!
她穿著鹘y的殖民服
She is dressed in traditional Colonial garb.
道e吧!我C了!
Say goodbye! We are going down!
保持冷o
Stay calm.
他m著我,C翼上有殖民D女
There is something they are not telling us.
There is a Colonial woman on the wing.
I will cover the pilot!
我硌谧ow行T!
她是l?她想要什N?
Who is she? What does she want?
我把它完成吧
Just let me make it up to you, please.
我跟f
I'm telling you,
的送Y一定很棒
your shower is going to be amazing.
我有一堆想
I have so many ideas.
我正想跟聊送Y
I want to talk to you about the shower.
我X得
I feel like
@已旱喘不^
it has been really overwhelming for you.
_始逼得失控
It's just starting to make you crazy.
小莉,我]事
No, Lil, I'm fine. I mean...
Lil, I'm fine.
K不好
No, you're not fine.
K不好,安妮
You are not fine, Annie,
F在_始,我需要
and we need things to just
平流M
flow smoothly from now on
海熟悉@N事
and Helen just knows how to do this kind of stuff.
她一直都在做@
She does it all the time.
非常擅L,也很芬
She is good at it. She likes doing it.
@就不必
This way you don't have to
聚餐或旅[了
plan any more lunches or trips.
不必勉槠潆y
You don't have to do anything you don't want to do.
我明白了
I get it.
我想λ投Y或其他事
I think it'll be best here on out
都有正面椭
for the shower and for everything.
好就好
Yeah, whatever you want.
能@邮亲詈玫
I mean, it's probably best.
我是@N想
I think so, right?
我只希望可以_心
Yeah. I just want you to be happy.
我想@游乙_心,扇其美
I think that will make me happy. It will be good.
就@
Okay. Okay.
太好了
Good.
Hey.
你想f聊?
Do you want to hang out?
不好笑喔!不要笑了
- It's not funny! - Stop laughing.
有c好笑
it's a little funny.
那些女孩]有人笑的出,相信我
None of those girls are laughing, believe me.
真的不好笑,你有被出wC^?
It's not funny. Have you ever been kicked off a plane?
有也不能f
I can't say that I have.
多x了
Thank you.
F在全部的人都很恨我
All of the girls hate me right now.
成了"O娘"
You are like the maid of dishonor.
我希望莉莉安的饽芸禳c消
I hope Lillian isn't going to be mad at me for too long.
,她不有事的
No, she will be all right.
不缘,希望事情能按他的想法走
I don't know, I just wish things were
the way that they used to be, you know.
I feel like her life is going off
我X得她的生命正在胎Q骨
o可挑剔,而我的就像…
and getting perfect, and mine is just like...
好D的
It will turn around, you know.
已了
I have been hearing that for a long time.
一定好D的,相信我
It's going to turn around. I just know it.
S便啦
Anyway.
要邮肿
You got to bake.
我真的不再碰了,f^了
I don't really do that any more, I told you.
槭颤N?
Why?
不知道,就…
I don't know, it's just...
不知道,破a後我就有想…
I don't know, after it just went under, I just, kind of,
收手了吧
stopped, I guess.
我不能吩谄渲
It doesn't make me happy any more.
不到X
Just because you didn't make any money at it,
不代表技不如人
doesn't mean that you failed at it.
我p失超多X
I lost a lot of money.
A家a
All my money.
但是身呀^技
But you are so good at it.
好啦,Q}吧
Oh, well. Let's change the subject.
不烘焙,我玩完了
No more baking. I'm done.
我不知道怎N^口不提
I don't know how you just can't do it any more.
如果我不再志察,我是…
If I wasn't a cop any more, I would still...
- 抓人? - О找人砩
Arrest people?
...Go out with a gun and shoot people.
I probably wouldn't do that. I'm just trying to make you feel better.
不真的做啦,只是哄你_心
]}的
You are okay, you know.
不太t解我
You don't know me very well.
知道K不差就蛄
I know you well enough to know that you're not so bad.
- 是有料的 - 是喔
You got some stuff. Oh, yeah.
要全方位L
You got bits and pieces going on.
x了
Thanks.
我已在打量了
I have been thinking about you a little bit.
我?真的?
About me? Really?
在想著一件事
There is something about you.
念念不忘的事
Something about you that sticks.
我o扣
- I hate buttons.
P室在哪?
Where is the bedroom?
- 抱歉,是登山 - ]事吧?
Sorry. It's a mountain bike. Are you okay?
喜gT越野?
Do you like mountain biking? Uh-huh.
掉@件
Take this off.
很_心美舫烧
I'm so glad this is happening.
我也是
So am I.
- 哈 - 早安
Hello. Morning.
抱歉,我不是故意醒的
Sorry, I didn't mean to freak you out.
]PS
No, it's okay.
我坐M久了
I haven't been sitting here that long. Oh.
抱歉,我睡太熟了
Sorry, I guess I fell asleep.
我不是故意要^夜的
I didn't mean to sleep over.
e傻了啦
Don't be silly.
我弄了一杯卡布奇Z
I made you a cappuccino.
- 你做的? -
Made it? Yeah.
昨晚真是良宵
So, last night was fun.
Π,非常_心
It was. It was very fun.
我很_心
I had fun.
炒得很火
It was fun.
如果想陪我去N房
If you care to accompany me to the kitchen,
g肪湍苎永m
the fun may continue.
不同的g
A different kind of fun.
但要不要穿c衣服
But why don't you just get dressed and whatever, and...
- 我把的衣服放在那 - 好的
I left your clothes over there.
Okay.
我就在N房等
And I'll see you in there.
好
Okay.
砝
There she is.
的烘焙屋迎候
Your workshop awaits.
我知道有c狂,但我不管了
I know it's a bit crazy, but I popped out
我各N都I了一c
and I got a few little baking bits and pieces.
奶油,牛奶
Butter, milk.
我想今天如果能一起做c心 很有趣
Because I thought that it would be fun for us to bake together today.
@然是在做c心
Obviously, you will be doing the baking.
我吃
I will be doing the eating.
因是＜
Because you are the expert.
我不想…
Yeah, I don't...
真的不想…
I don't really wanna...
抱歉,你大M周章,但是…
Sorry. You went to all this trouble, but...
砺,我知道有c生疏 但是很好吃的
Come on, I know you haven't done it in a while, but it'll be great.
e傻了,快邮职,的ｉL耶
Don't be silly, just get into it. You are so good at it.
好,我懂了
All right. I get it.
F在是w力下滑
It was a bit of a curve ball.
,我想走了
Yeah, I think I'm going to go.
很抱歉,我是走了
I'm sorry. I should just probably go.
安妮
Annie,
我不知道在不爽什N
I don't know what you are getting so upset about.
因不懂我
Because you don't know me.
根本不知道我是l,我的情r
You don't know anything about me or my life or...
- 因椤 - 我不知道你的目的
Well, no, because... I don't know what you're trying to do here.
- 我不需要你臀 - ?
I don't need you to fix me. To fix you?
我不需要任何f助,你以槟闶钦l?
I don't need any help. I mean, who do you think you are?
才一切都很好,F在s180度…
Jesus, Annie, we had a really good time. And now you are being all...
我的e,我昨晚不去找的
It's my fault. I shouldn't have come here last night.
昨晚是e`
Last night was a mistake.
去死啦,好吧
Fucking hell. All right.
我是莉莉安,袈後_始留言,
Hey, it's Lillian. Leave a message after the beep.
小莉,是我
Hey, Lil, it's me.
Umm...
我_定在馕,但]有
I'm sure you're probably still a little bit mad at me, but I hope not.
好啦,刺激的事]Y束
Anyway, the excitement still continues with me.
我跟r下我的警察睡
I just slept with a cop that pulled me over
早上醒磲,他很N心,很H切
and I woke up today, and he was really sweet and nice and cute.
然後本能反,我就快Wx_了
So, naturally, I ran out as fast as I could.
我是怎N了?
What's wrong with me?
Umm...
好啦,我知道忙翻天
Anyway, I know you are busy and stuff,
所以有空的再回我
so just call me when you get a chance.
方便的,我很芬飧把v_
I'd love to talk this out with you when you can.
好了,掰
Okay, bye.
安妮!起床
Annie! Annie, wake up.
早上11c了
It's 11:00 a.m.
R的
Oh, shit.
有包裹
You got a package.
我想拿o,但f"e碰我的|西"
I'd bring it to you, but you said, "Don't touch my things."
g迎加入我的巴黎茶m
Please join us for a Parisian brunch
至海哈里士三世的家
at the home of Helen Harris lll
c祝莉莉安c道格拉斯的婚Y
to celebrate the marriage of Lillian Donovan and Douglas Price.
c莉莉安一同分享Y物c 等您回覆喔,啦!
Let us shower Lillian with gifts and love. Répondez s'il vous plait. Yay!
- 不好意思 - 嗨
Excuse me. Oh. Hi.
我在臀业穆榧I生日Y物
I'm looking for a birthday gift for my best friend. Oh.
我想送他,上面"永h的麻吉"
I want to get her a necklace that says, "Best Friends Forever."
_定要加"永h"?
You sure you want it to say "Forever"?
,怎?
Yeah, why?
拜,"永h"?
Come on. "Forever"?
永h
Forever.
我不J是永h的麻吉,o意冒犯
I don't think you guys will be best friends forever. No offense.
但是…
But you know...
在年pr候交的朋友…
The friends you have when you are younger sometimes...
L大後,自l展
Sometimes you grow apart when you get older.
她有可能找到新的麻吉
Maybe she'll find a new best friend.
她也S比更成功
And maybe she will be more successful than you are
更漂亮,更有X,更苗l
and prettier and richer and skinnier
然後她就永h在一起了
and they end up doing everything together.
很怪
You are weird.
我不怪好?
I'm not weird. Okay?
很怪
Yes, you are.
我不怪,是_始的
No, I'm not, and you started it.
e,是_始的
No, you started it.
是不是早上忘了吃精神?
Did you forget to take your Xanax this morning?
天啊,我替的爸感到y^
God, I feel bad for your parents.
我替的感到y^
I feel bad for your face.
等L了奶子再找我
Okay, well, call me when your boobs come in.
等的奶子大再找我
You call me when yours come in.
- 什N,有4男友? - ]e
What, do you have four boyfriends? Exactly.
那祝在舞後生小
Yeah, okay, have fun having a baby at your prom.
就像老巫婆
You look like an old mop.
K]有想像中受g迎
You know what? You're not as popular as you think you are.
我是f人迷
I am very popular.
我想也是啦
I'm sure you are.
超受g迎
Very popular.
是一位又老,又孤
Well, you're an old, single loser
又]有任何朋友的☆
who is never going to have any friends.
@小v人
You're a little cunt.
Σ黄
I'm sorry.
由我砀嬖V我
Let me tell my mom, okay.
我已告V她了
I already told her.
她有抓狂?
Was she mad?
嗨,安妮 又我是,_
Hi, Annie, it's Rhodes again.
既然都不回
Since you're not returning any of my calls,
我就不想再跟我相了,也好
I assume that you're not interested
in spending any more time with me, which is fine.
So don't worry, I won't be bothering you ever again.
e心,我不再打_了
去修好尾舭
Get those taillights fixed.
我不再邀和我住了
We'd like to invite you to no longer live with us any more.
什N意思?我不懂
What? What do you mean? I don't get it.
就是f,我JΤ赡晷置枚言
The thing is, we decided that it was actually a bit immature
跟室友同住K不怎N成熟
for a grown-up brother and sister to
still be living together with a roommate.
At our age, it's a bit ridiculous, isn't it? Yeah.
- 在@年o有c荒唐Π? -
- 我感X有c笨,Π? - 很可悲
We look a bit silly, don't we? Pathetic.
所以我想立生活
So we are actually going to live together alone.
不包括
Without you.
要搬走了
You're moving out.
她不右
She's not moving.
她的
She will move.
- 究的 - 究的
Eventually. Eventually.
她一定要
She has to.
她接受的
She is taking it in.
得x_
You have to leave.
好扎喔
Oh! That's prickly.
- 嗨 - 嗨
Hi. Hi.
得f我碰到谷底?
Remember when you thought I hit bottom?
那不到
That wasn't bottom.
^戆
Come here.
要想_c,我倒是g迎回
We're gonna have fun. I, for one, am really glad you're here.
猜怎N著?
And guess what?
rC洽洽好
Good timing.
知道今天影У晁褪颤N片子?
You know what just came in today on the Netflix?
浩劫重生,姆h克斯演
Cast Away. Tom Hanks.
就像阿甘正,只是在u上
It's like Forrest Gump, but on an island.
H鄣,喜g的
Honey, you are gonna love it.
我的老天
My God.
@是她的私人道?
This is her driveway?
@人是l?
Who is that man?
您是海哈里斯三世的客人?
Are you a guest of Helen Harris III?
栏碇v,是的
Yes. Technically. I guess.
S在R等您
An attendant will meet you at the stables.
怎N走?
Where?
送Y鲈诘诙座
The shower is over the second bridge.
- 粉t檬水? - xx你
Pink lemonade? Thank you.
我]有置杯架,我可以…
I don't have a cup holder. Can I just give that...
粉t檬水,真w面
Pink lemonade. Nice. Nice touch.
可
Shit.
死,真好喝
God damn it, that's good.
Mmm.
R的,真新r
Shit, that is fresh.
@是我看^最漂亮的送Y
This is the most beautiful shower I have ever been to.
她分送超可鄣男《Y物
Yes, and Helen is giving out the cutest party favors.
Π,我喜的粉t雷帽
I know, I love their pink berets.
- 需要睃c香? - 好
Would you like some champagne? Yes.
法的
It's French.
安妮
Annie. Hey.
嗨
Hi.
好?出F了
How are you doing? You're here.
我出F了,我被邀的,抱歉
Yeah, I'm here. I was invited. Sorry.
然邀,我是f砹
Of course you were invited. I just meant you have arrived.
我是_玩笑的
No, I was just joking. Okay.
敢相信?美O了Π?
Can you believe this? Isn't it amazing?
Yep.
真不
Yeah. it's nice.
很漂亮
Yeah. Pretty.
]事吧?
Are we okay?
很抱歉我]回
Yes, I'm sorry I haven't called.
- 我不想逃避 - 原我,那太狂了
I just didn't want to bug you, but...
Forgive me. It just got crazy.
There has been lots of organizing, and... I have so much to tell you.
@e有很多事要弄,我很想去告V的
我得跟我姑打招呼,不然她恨我
I have to say hi to my aunt or she will get mad at my mom.
,要到招呼
No, you gotta go do your party rounds.
Yeah.
我R上就碚
I'll see you in a minute.
好的
Yeah. Okay.
塔,送我毛巾
Oh! Rita, you got all our towels.
,因槲啊,小咪
Yes, I did. Because I love you, Kitten.
好啦,看下一吧
All right, let's see what's next.
下一
Another one, another one, another one.
我知道@是l的了,我先uP子
I know who this is from. I can tell by the wrapping.
的?
Is that you?
安妮,是做的
Annie, you made this.
看
Look.
- 啊 - 我的天啊
- Oh, man. - Oh, my gosh.
是我,安妮
It's us, Annie.
- 天啊 - 我看看
- Oh, my God. - Let me see.
我的老天
Oh, my God.
@是密瓦基所有商店e我最喜g的
This is all my favorite stuff from all the stores I love in Milwaukee.
安妮!真是o法置信
Annie! This is so unbelievable.
威森菲利普
Wilson Phillips.
我弁森菲利普
Man, I love Wilson Phillips.
在我考到汽{照r
We listened to Hold On probably 10,000 times
我了上千次"巫"
when I got my driver's license.
@Y物真是太棒了
This is such an amazing gift.
- xx - 不客
Thank you. You're welcome.
我深感抱歉,小莉
I feel really bad, Lil,
我在]空涠Y物
I didn't get a chance to actually get you a present
因槲乙恢倍荚诿λ投Y
because I have been so busy organizing the shower.
海,拜,@泳蛄
Helen, please. It's more than enough.
@是恭R的卡片
Here is a card to say congratulations.
xx,做的已蚨嗔
Thank you. Gosh, you have really outdone yourself.
我的老天,海
Oh, my God, Helen.
H鄣,是什N?
Honey, what is it?
海我去巴黎
Helen's taking me to Paris.
的表情!
Your face!
中了,被我整了
I got you. I fooled you.
看的表情
Look at your face.
只是先小放婚假,到了巴黎
It's just a little pre-wedding vacation. And while we're there,
我要拜O,穿Y服
we're gonna meet the designer of her dress and have a fitting.
要我去巴黎?
You are taking me to Paris?
天啊!@是史上最棒的Y物!
Oh, my God! This is the best present ever!
太感x了
Thank you so much.
一巴黎!
A Paris!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
他的在耍我?
Are you fucking kidding me?
- 安妮! - 不行,
Annie! No, Mom.
去他的巴黎?
Motherfucking Paris?
安妮,在致?
Annie, what are you doing?
是我f要用巴黎的,我告@整想
I told you about Paris, Helen. I told you about this whole idea!
- 安妮,冷o - 不行,莉莉安
- Annie, calm down. - No, Lillian!
怎?想跟海去巴黎了?
What, you're gonna go to Paris with Helen now?
要T著FR
What, you guys are gonna ride around on bikes
戴著雷帽同[
with berets and fucking baguettes
@子放著法I包?
in the basket of the front of your bikes?
真是浪漫!
How romantic!
什N女人和e的女人同[巴黎?
What woman gives another woman a trip to Paris?
我]e的?是蕾z
Am I right? Lesbian.
- 大家都@NJ榘? - 我不是
We're all thinking it, aren't we? I'm not.
- 我是 - 大家都@NJ榘?
Okay? Yes, we're all thinking it, right? I was.
- 安妮 - 莉莉安,@不是我JR的
Annie... Lillian, this is not the "you" that I know.
我JR的是D身M,翻白眼
The "you" that I know would have
walked in here and rolled your eyes
f@直太超^了,可笑又愚蠢
and thought this was completely
over-the-top, ridiculous and stupid.
Look at this shower! Look at that fucking cookie!
看看@!看看那c心!
真以檫@群女人可以嗑光甜c?
Did you really think that this group of women
was going to finish that cookie?
Really? You know what? That reminds me, actually.
@倒是提醒我
我]L^死的甜c
I never got a chance to try that fucking cookie!
白目甜c
Stupid fucking cookie!
真好吃!c心,我X得…
Delicious! Stupid cookie. I think I'll...
沾c巧克力更棒
Maybe it's better if I dip it in the chocolate.
@就是要的,莉莉安?
is this what you want, Lillian?
真是太正c了
This is so awesome.
大家岷艉舻f巧克力吧
All right, let's have some nice, hot, unsanitary chocolate!
好C喔!我的呀!
Ahh! It's hot! Jesus! God!
天啊,安妮,是l了?
Christ, Annie. Have you lost your fucking mind?
- 在致? - 我在致?
What are you doing? What am I doing?
不知道Π?人在哪?
You wouldn't know, would you? Where have you been?
不明白的,我砘卮
You would have no idea. Let me fill you in, okay?
婚後,一切就走恿
Ever since you got engaged, everything has turned to shit!
我告V,@本砭褪俏业r光
You know what? This is supposed to be about my time!
我每次活都O法У,多啦
You have managed to ruin every event
in my wedding. Thank you very much.
Okay, well, thank you very much.
感x提醒我
@都是她的e,不是我!
It's all her fault. It is not mine!
而且lF
And you would know that,
如果把美蛋塞^屁眼
if you got your beautiful haired head out of your asshole.
f是塞她的屁眼,肯定白o瑕
In fact, out of her asshole, which I'm sure is perfectly bleached.
我告V,]e!
You know what? It is!
我是怎N知道的?
And you know how I know?
因槲腋她去^理d
Because I went to the fucking salon with her
我B我的屁眼也染白
and I got my asshole bleached, too!
我喜畚业男缕ㄑ!
And I love my new asshole!
何不先槲c祝
You know what? Why can't you just be happy for me
回家後再偷偷怨我?就像平常人
and then go home and talk behind my back later, like a normal person?
我祝福,莉莉安,我真心祝福
I am happy for you, Lillian. I am very happy for you.
最好,我不再打_了
I wish you well. I won't bother you any more.
在跟我_玩笑?安妮
Are you kidding me? Annie!
快^去
Go, go, go, go, go!
快回!站住
Get back here! Stop.
不要!她]渑π《Y物
No, no! She does not get a party favor.
她]渌凸
She does not get a dog!
如果要搞@套
And if you are going to act like this,
那就e砦业幕槎Yv蛋
then don't even bother coming to my wedding!
- 我以s,小莉 - ]嘴,海!
I'm proud of you, Lil.
Shut up, Helen!
Anybody else have anything they want to share today?
有人想要分享其他事?
我已ё2b狗,在我的後箱
I took two dogs already. They're in the back of my van.
什N?
What?
不吧?你想跑去哪?
What? Where are you going?
肇事逃逸!秀!
Hit and run! Classy!
好拥!
Perfect! Okay.
我追到你的,我砹!
I'm gonna find you! I'm coming!
拜!
Come on! Come on! Come on.
不!
No!
操
Shit.
我K不意外
I can't say I'm surprised.
我告V去修舻
I did tell you to get your lights fixed.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
F在}就砹
And now here we are.
著,我^了恐怖的一天
Look, I have had a horrible day.
我不需要你F在ξ艺f教
I don't need a lecture from you right now, okay?
我…海她…
I just... Helen just...
好了
Oh! Don't...
@和海]PS
This didn't happen because of Helen.
是因的後]修好才l生的
This happened because you didn't get your taillights fixed.
很渭
It's pretty simple.
知道每天晚上看_著
Do you have any idea how frustrating it is
尾牡舻能_^去有多另人沮?
to see you, night by night, drive past me
with your fucking taillights still broken?
Do you have any idea how crazy that makes me?
有想^我快被逼了?
答案很
It's a simple solution!
的},安妮
Your problem, Annie,
是不知道p害到e人
is that you just don't understand that you can hurt people
with these broken lights.
Don't you see how irresponsible this is?
不知道@是不任?
,我是修好舻
Yes, I should have gotten my fucking taillights fixed.
但我]有好?我]有
But I didn't, okay? I didn't.
著,e心
Listen, don't worry about it.
我f真的,鬟_的事我有收到
Seriously. Your message was received.
拜啦,我不知道F在是怎恿
No, look, please, I don't know what's going on with me right now.
]事,e 真的,覆水y收
Look, it's fine. Don't bother. Really, what's done is done.
就@?你要去哪?
That's it? Where are you going?
就@!公事公k
That's it! That's it. That's how this works.
拜,我不…
Come on. I didn't...
根o,挑逗我
For the record, Annie, you flirted with me.
我以真心喜g我
You made me feel like you really liked me,
非常不公平
which was really unfair.
然後跟我回家做那n事,~水之g
And then you came home with me and we did stuff, fun stuff,
事後就x_,好像oPo要
and then you just left, just like it was nothing.
拜,我知道男人的目的
Oh, please. I know how guys do this thing.
我知道男人的e
I know how guys act.
前一分f@,下一分就
One minute, it means something. The next minute, it doesn't.
- ,已摸清男人底 - 好吧
Right, yeah, you've got it all figured out.
Yeah.
那成效如何?Md而w?
How is that working out for you? Pretty good?
Boom!
怎,情D,f要路道救援?
What's up, fuck-buddy? You call for some roadside assistance?
x了,警察,之後的事我硖理
Thanks, officer. I can handle it from here on out.
行行好!
Come on!
我也只能找他,我又不知道你出F
I didn't have anyone else to call!
I didn't know that you were gonna show up!
@是警察的}
That's the problem with cops, Annie.
我^不在有需要r才F身
We're just never there when you need us.
那l子f怪怪的
That cop talks weird.
上了,傻婆 r光流逝,我有事要忙
- Come on, dingus. Tick-tock. I got shit to do.
看好,是什N在操控方向P
Check it out. Look what's steering the car.
再次感x你斫游
Thanks again for picking me up.
不成}
Not a problem.
你在忙?
Were you busy?
今天是星期五
Well, it is Friday.
好像很累喔
You know, you look tired.
累的,可以在我的跨下躺平
If you're tired, you can totally
有d趣的
lay down in my lap, if you want.
什N?
What?
就在腿上小[一下
Just take a little lap-nap.
有d趣的
If you want.
人情
Open for biz.
你可以停在路?
Okay, can you just pull over?
然可以,@更好
Yeah, actually, that's an even better idea.
不是,可以你停下,我想下
No, no, no, can you please just stop the car? I want to get out.
不行,@e超抖的
No, it's super gravelly.
- 拜路停 - 怎N了?
Please pull over! Why?
因槲被\
Because I would rather get murdered out here
也不要再花半小r陪你
than spend the next half-an-hour with you.
可以你路停?
Can you please just pull over?
拜,安妮,那叫幽默
Come on, Annie. It's called humor.
W著c
Learn about it.
而且我尾坏桨胄r
Besides, I would never last a half-hour.
再,泰德
Good bye, Ted.
如果F在臀"u"淼眉
If you're trying to turn me on, it's working.
在利用我
You used me!
不成夂,不再是我的3情D
No big deal. You are no longer my number three!
威森!
Wilson!
威森!我Σ黄鹉!
Wilson! I'm sorry!
Σ黄,威森
I'm sorry, Wilson.
威森,Σ黄!
Wilson, I'm sorry!
Σ黄!
I'm sorry!
不要啊,威森
Oh, no, Wilson.
威森!
Wilson!
我M
I'm coming in.
M去,M去,我在散步
Let's go, let's go. And we're walking.
我在散步,跟上,跟上!
Okay, we're walking. Heel. Heel!
不准尿!不能在地毯上
No pee. No! Not on the carpet!
我M
Okay, we're coming... We're coming in.
全都M去好好玩吧
Everybody is in and having fun.
乖乖玩,跟上去
We're having fun. And heel! We're heeling.
跟上!
Heel!
共纂b?
How many of those did you take?
ё6b
I took nine.
要ё咚有狗我是有c荷不了
Yeah, I did slightly over-commit to the whole dog thing.
最後,大概6b我^能付
It turns out, I'm probably more comfortable with six.
要用很大的力肀
It's a lot... That's a lot of energy to deal with.
但不知道^程的
But you wouldn't know anything about that,
因槟愣]回我
because you haven't been returning my calls.
要f什N,梅根
And say what, Megan?
f"嗨,我x不_沙l"
Say, "Hi, I can't get off the couch.
"我被o了,我被踢出公寓了"
"I got fired from my job. I got kicked out of my apartment.
"我付不起,我的子成了UF"
"I can't pay any of my bills. My car is a piece of shit.
"我]有任何朋友,最後一次…"
"I don't have any friends. The last time
我lF一件有趣的事,安妮
You know what I find interesting about that, Annie?
我X得f的真是有趣
It's interesting to me that you have absolutely no friends.
知道槭颤N有趣?
You know why it's interesting?
@e有朋友就站在面前
Here's a friend standing directly
跟f
in front of you, trying to talk to you.
而_要f]有任何朋友
And you choose to talk about the fact
that you don't have any friends.
- 知道我的意思 - ,我不X得需要椭
You know what I mean.
No, I don't think you want any help.
- 我X得想搞孤癖趴 - ]@回事
I think you want to have a little pity party. That's not true.
我X得安妮想搞孤癖趴
I think Annie wants a little pity party.
- 是混蛋,安妮! - 在致?
You're an asshole, Annie! Oh, my God. What are you doing?
是混蛋,我是人生 人生打_了?
You're an asshole. I'm life. Is life bothering you?
-  - 在致?
Yes! What are you doing?
我是人生,安妮
I'm life, Annie. I'm life, Annie.
- 得抵抗人生 - 在致?
You have got to fight back on life.
- 梅根! - 最好W抵抗
Megan!
You better learn to fight.
- 梅根! - 我是人生,我⒁的屁股!
Megan!
I'm life and I'm going to bite you in the ass!
Megan... it's not me. I'm your life. Turn over!
- 梅根 - 那不是我,我是的人生,D^去!
天啊!
My God!
我要抗可悲的人生
I'm trying to get you to fight for your shitty life, and you won't do it!
- 就是不要! - 住手
You just won't do it. Stop it.
停止自打耳光!
You stop slapping yourself. Stop slapping yourself.
我是的人生,我是可悲的…
I'm your life, Annie. I'm your shitty...
Σ黄
I'm sorry.
p的好
Nice hit.
太好了
All right.
很c幸c燃了小火苗
I'm glad to see you've got a little bit of spark in you.
我知道^去的安妮就藏在某e
I knew that Annie was in there somewhere.
我想…
I think...
我想蚋衤一位女生的故事了
I think you're ready now to hear a little story about a girl.
一位名叫梅根的女生
A girl named Megan.
梅根的高中生活K不美好
A girl named Megan that didn't have
a very good time in high school.
I'm referring to myself when I say "Megan."
我f"梅根"r,就代表我本人
- 就是我,梅根 - 我明白
It's me, Megan. Yeah, I got that.
我知道想f
I know you look at me now and think,
"好小子,她高中肯定好整以暇"
"Boy, she must have breezed through high school."
^非如此,安妮
Not the case, Annie.
@幼右上下跑教室^非易事
No, this was not easy going up and down the halls. Okay?
他常想炸掉我
They used to try to blow me up.
他G鞭炮到我^上
They threw firecrackers at my head.
鞭炮
Firecrackers.
我是f真的,不是在比喻
I mean literally. I'm not saying that figuratively.
我的^上被G鞭炮,他叫我怪物
I got firecrackers thrown at my head. They called me a freak.
J槲矣斜淮虻?
Do you think I let that break me?
J槲跑回家找哭著f
Do you think I went home to my mommy, crying,
"我一朋友都]有,梅根]有任何朋友"
"I don't have any friends. Megan doesn't have any friends"?
我K]有,知道我怎N做?
No, I did not. You know what I did?
我自己站起,lD
I pulled myself up, I studied really hard.
x遍D^的,F在呢?
I read every book in the library. And now?
我了公T
I work for the government. I have
我@得最高C密的Y格
the highest possible security clearance.
- 不要重覆 - 我不
Don't repeat that! I won't.
我保o不了
I can't protect you.
我知道所有核的位置c用艽a
I know where all the nukes are and I know the codes.
我^ΡＣ
I won't say anything.
傻眼
You would be amazed.
很多g的物中心
A lot of shopping malls.
不要重覆!
Don't repeat that!
我不
I won't.
我有6g屋子
I have six houses.
月前我I了一部18,因槲矣心芰
I bought an 18-wheeler a couple of months ago just because I could.
失去莉莉安
Okay, you lost Lillian.
s交到另一位麻吉
You got another best friend
就坐在前面,如果有注意到的
sitting right in front of you, if you would notice.
Huh?
F在要停止自
Now, you got to stop feeling sorry for yourself.
我不怨天尤人
Okay, 'cause I do not associate with people
that blame the world for their problems.
'Cause you're your problem, Annie.
因}出在,安妮
解M人
And you're also your solution.
好?@就是…
Right? I mean, that's...
懂了?
You get that?
我失去她了
I just miss her, I guess.
,我知道
Yeah, I know you do.
我知道
I know you do.
好啦,接受它吧
All right, come on. Bring it in.
我JR…
There's the Annie...
我JR的安妮在@
There's the Annie I knew was there, okay?
好了 天啊!要去洗^了
All right. Man, you have got to wash your hair.
Σ黄
I'm sorry.
要去洗^了
You've got to wash that hair.
怎N了?
What's wrong?
]事
Nothing.
我
I love you.
好看多了,xx
Looks great. Thank you.
以前_和我有立^契,所以本店奉送
Rhodes and I worked out a deal way back when, so it's on the house.
你是f真的?
Are you serious?
,我欠他太多了
Yeah. I owe him big time.
真是太好心了
That's really nice.
?
Hey, Mom?
@是我,茱蒂
This is my mom, Judy.
好?幸了
Hey, how are you? Nice to meet you.
幸幸
Good to meet you, too.
等等,我在戒酒o名看^Π?
Wait a minute, don't I know you from AA?
天啊,香草沾u就是做的吧?
Oh, my gosh. You made that artichoke dip, didn't you?
不e吧?
It's good, huh?
真是太好吃了
It's just delicious.
M
Come in.
_定今天不跟我去?
Are you sure you're not gonna come with me today?
莉莉安的大喜之日
It's Lillian's big day.
,她不希望我出F
Mom, she doesn't want me there.
我漉n~三明治
I'll fix you a tuna fish sandwich.
,才早上8c
Mom, it's 8:00 in the morning.
可以加c糖{
You can put syrup on it.
我知道
I know.
嗨
Hi.
想致?
What do you want?
我在想不知道莉莉安在哪
I was wondering if you knew where Lillian was.
不知道,槭颤N我… 怎Nf?
No, why would I... What do you mean?
我到都找不到她
I can't find her. We've looked everywhere.
怎N?
What?
她失了,能兔?
She is missing. Can you help?
好,就在@等
Okay, just wait here. I think I know
我知道有人可以兔φ
someone that might be able to help.
- 我要去拿匙 - 我可以…
I'll get my Keys. Can I just use...
我不缘眠有哪h出e
I mean, I just don't know what could have possibly gone wrong.
一切都很利
Everything was going smoothly.
Y服@NA,是巴黎M口
The dress looked fantastic. It had come in from Paris.
小道也]有钣趾兔
Dougie was being great and very helpful.
我也o密鼓渲
I had organized everything to the last final detail.
就是…
I just...
我不知道她是怎N了
I don't know what's happened to her.
我不知道,知道吧?
I don't know. You should know, right?
是她的麻吉,不知道才怪
You're her best friend. It's weird that you don't know.
那NH近
You guys are so close.
安妮,我要H自向道歉
Annie, I want to apologize to you personally
λ有l生^的事道歉
for all of the things that have gone down.
我知道我了
I know that I hurt you,
在和莉莉安疏h
and that I created a distance between you and Lillian.
- 很抱歉@些… - 我不想…
I want to apologize for that... I don't want to hear...
在送Yl生的事
...and everything that happened
有拉斯S加斯…
at the shower. And with Las Vegas...
好了,我真的不想
Okay, I don't want to hear any more, honestly.
甚至不想跟v
I don't even want to talk to you.
哈利也奈聪胝J真我f
Harry never really wants to talk to me, either.
他好像整年都要旅行
He travels a lot. Like, all year.
基本上我都靠自己
I'm basically just by myself.
我不替感到y^
I don't want to... I don't feel sorry for you.
我真的喜g在婚店挑的那套Y服
I really liked that original dress
you picked at the bridal store.
I thought it was beautiful. You have really lovely taste.
我X得那很漂亮,的品味非常可
多x,但r已晚
Thanks, but it's a little too late for that.
我知道…
And I know...
我不J榘臀魇澄镌斐纱蠹沂澄镏卸
I don't think that Brazilian food really gave us food poisoning.
的_是
NO, it did.
我不J槭
No, I don't think it did.
就是食物,我在回家路上也拉在子上
It was the food. I shit my pants on the way home.
我不X得那是的e
I don't think it was your fault.
就是我的e
That was my fault.
大家拜我婚Y的事
I think people just ask me to their weddings
是因槲疑瞄Lk派
because I'm good at organizing parties.
我]有任何女性朋友
I don't have any female friends.
真是抱歉
I'm so sorry.
槭颤N在笑,安妮?
Why are you smiling, Annie?
只是…
It's just... It's just...
第一次看到如此的h
It's the first time I've ever seen you look ugly.
@我有c爽
And that makes me kind of happy.
我很h?]有,我K]有非常h
I look ugly? No, I don't. I don't really look ugly.
- 有一c,很h的I人,但]PS - 我不是很h的I人
A little bit. You're an ugly crier, but that's okay.
No, I'm not really an ugly crier.
Maybe just a little bit. No.
也S真有一c
有一cc
Just a little bit.
那是我的化y品
It's just my makeup.
但我是很漂亮
But I still look pretty good.
_!
Rhodes!
_
Rhodes.
拜!_!
Come on! Rhodes!
- 他不理 -
He's ignoring you. Let me. Yes, he is.
警察!u下窗!
- Officer! - Roll down your window!
打_一下!拜!
Excuse me! Please!
_ 我知道你得到,我知道你在馕
Rhodes, I know you can hear me, and I know you're mad at me,
但我需要你兔,拜!
but I need your help. Please!
JR@人?
You know this guy?
要做什N?
What are you doing?
我想引起他的注意
I just want to get his attention.
安妮!我的天啊
Annie! Oh, my God.
危U{!
Reckless driving!
安妮,我的^!你在致?
Annie, my hair! What are you doing?
我超速了!最好r下我!
I'm speeding! You better pull me over!
真的?
Really?
yG垃圾的人砹!
Here comes the litter-bug!
看看v狗的行
Let's see what Marmaduke's doing.
骱,_v手C
Just texting. Talking on the phone while I'm driving.
不是用手_ 喂,您好!
Not even using my hands. Oh, hi!
Mmm! Yum! Yum!
啤酒!
Beer!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
智障
Idiot.
嘿,老兄怎?
Hey, what's up, man?
不在乎,不在乎
I don't care. I don't care.
我快被甩出去了,我真的很,安妮
I'm going to hurl. I feel really sick, Annie!
咦!是l在_?
Hey, who's driving that car?
F在可以起身了?
Can we go up now?
真不明智
That's not clever.
Hey!
上空秀喔!
I'm topless!
我一z不
I'm totally topless.
碚娴?
Really?
o法置信
Wow. Unbelievable.
在搞什N鬼|西?
What the fuck are you doing?
不知道
I don't know.
了?
Hey! Are you crazy?
Are you crazy?
@些行槎伎赡茏{人身陷危C
All of that stuff, that would have been dangerous for a good driver.
Σ黄,我是真的需要你兔
I'm sorry. I just... I really need your help.
我找不到莉莉安
We can't find Lillian.
她不多久了?
How long has she been gone?
她失12小r了
She's been missing for 12 hours.
12小r?
12 hours?
至少24小r才算是失人口
It's not a missing person until it's at least 24 hours.
有]有看^CSI?要24小r
Have you ever seen CSI? 24 hours.
我要^m糖诹,安妮
Let me get on with my job, Annie.
拜啦,南森?
Nathan, please?
我是真的需要你兔
I really need your help.
拜,南森
Please, Nathan.
@位是l?
Who is this one?
- 他是海 - 我叫海
This is Helen. I'm Helen.
- 什N? - 是海
What?
It's Helen.
哈,海,我有^精采的故事
Hello, Helen. I've heard wonderful things.
x了,兄弟,再
Okay, thanks, buddy. Bye-bye.
我追到她的手C
Okay, we've traced her cell phone
在奎那和_z街的D角
to the corner of Craner and Rose.
知道在哪?
Do you know where that is?
知道,是她的公寓
Yes. That is her apartment.
- f找^那了 - _有,在昨晚
I thought you said you looked there.
We did. We did. Last night.
好吧
Okay.
是f她在她的公寓e?
So you're saying she's at her apartment? That's what you're telling me?
- 她一定是在x_後回去的 - 她快了
She must have gone back after you left.
God, that was crazy of her.
Thank God! Thank you. Let's go. Let's go.
- x天x地!感x您,快走 - 好
Okay.
We found her!
我找到她了!
很抱歉,不是故意要浪M你的rg
I am so sorry. I didn't mean to waste your time.
真是不好意思
That's embarrassing.
- xx你 - 不客
Thank you. No, you are welcome.
就是@N幽
It's this kind of high-octane stuff
我想成榫察的
that really made me want to become a cop.
"失女孩在她的住找到了"
"Missing girl found at her apartment."
真是…
It's...
真是血}
It's adrenalin-pinching.
很_心到你
It's nice to see you.
很高d去修好尾袅
I'm glad that you got your taillights fixed.
代表我不用再r了
Means I won't have to stop you again.
了解
Okay.
安妮,快走啊
Annie, let's go.
好啦,快去朋友的公寓救她吧
Anyway, go and save your friend from her apartment.
再
Bye-bye.
掰
Bye.
可以我一人去就好?
Do you mind actually if I go by myself?
]}
Sure. Okay.
小莉?
Lil?
莉莉安?
Lillian?
小莉?
Lil?
L_
Go away.
怎N了?
What happened?
整婚Y都被搞砸了
This whole wedding is fucked up.
海什N都要管
Helen just took over everything, and
全都失控了
everything's got out of control.
我老爸不起婚Y
And my dad can't afford the wedding.
真的很y]有
This has been really hard to do without you.
一Fy
It's been shitty.
Σ黄
I'm sorry.
不,是我不
Nope. I'm sorry.
很抱歉把踢出去
I'm sorry I kicked you out of my wedding.
我的e
It's my fault.
不,是我的e
No, it's my fault.
我X得我神有}
I think I'm the one with the mental problems.
到我吧?新娘是抓狂的
Yeah, wasn't it my turn to be crazy?
The bride's supposed to be crazy.
-  - 栏碚f
Yes, technically.
- 偷走我的狂 - 我用掉了
You kind of stole all the crazy. I out-crazied you.
一切都]事的
Everything's going to be okay.
真的?怎N知道?
Yeah? How do you know that?
昨晚我牟逝啪x_後
I left the rehearsal dinner last night.
我告V小道我要去I棉花棒
I told Dougie I had to go get Q-tips.
然後
And
突然g,我lX我_到@e
all of a sudden, I realized I was driving here.
我回到@e
I came here.
我lX@⑹亲钺嵋淮
I realized this is the last time I'm going to be here
回到公寓
in this apartment
坐在沙l
with that couch,
床上睡
and this bed,
在浴缸洗澡了
and take a bath in my bathtub.
知道我有多圻@浴缸的
Because you know how much I love my bathtub.
很舒m的浴缸
It's a good tub.
我30q的生日就睡在那,得吧?
I slept in there on my 30th birthday, remember? Uh-huh.
一切都⒆了
Everything's gonna change.
]有我尾贿^5分
I mean, I'm not going to get to
live five minutes away from you.
And it makes me so sad.
想到@我就非常心
e@
Well, don't be.
e心,m然即⒏淖
Don't be sad. Because things are going to change,
但明天更好
but they'll be better.
t解吧?
You know?
要跨出@ゴ,美的一步
You're gonna take this huge, great, beautiful step.
小道全心全意的
And Dougie loves you more than anything.
我也啊
And so do I.
但怎Nk?不有}?
But what about you? What's gonna happen to you?
我好好^的
I'm gonna be fine.
就e心了好?
So don't worry, okay? I'm gonna be...
我好好^的
I'm gonna be fine.
我]事
I am fine.
而且要我的火^
And besides, you need to blaze the trail for me.
回笄胺桨l生什N事
And then report back and tell me what's coming.
f的算,老
Whatever you say, boss.
好啦,我去穿婚吧
All right, let's get your dress on,
好,快s去的婚Y
okay, and let's go to your wedding.
好啦
Oh, yeah.
@又是另一}
That's the other problem.
不准笑
Don't you dare laugh.
好吧
Okay.
我不能穿@套啦
I cannot wear this dress!
好,e慌
Okay, don't panic.
直就是
This is a nightmare.
我可以搞定的
We'll fix it.
砟X筋急D
We'll tweak it.
除非美到o可挑剔
I will not let you walk down that aisle
否t我是不走下去的,我保C
unless you look perfect and beautiful, I promise.
有和?
Do you have a chainsaw and a blowtorch?
我X得@龌槎Y是一碾y
I think this wedding is gonna be a disaster.
e貘f嘴
No, don't say that.
如果海做好f全
If Helen had anything to do with this wedding,
婚Y高F又典雅
it is going to be perfect and tasteful and beautiful.
倒是真的
That's true.
道格拉斯,您意娶莉莉安槠
Will you, Douglas, take Lillian to be your wife?
K深鬯,安慰她,守o她
Will you love her, comfort her, and keep her
喑一切s念,在晌挥猩之年
and, forsaking all others, remain true to her
至\待她?
as long as you both shall live?
我意
I do.
莉莉安,您意嫁o道格拉斯槟的丈夫
And will you, Lillian, take Douglas to be your husband?
K深鬯,安慰他
Will you love him, comfort him, and keep him
在晌挥猩之年守o著他?
as long as you both shall live?
我意
I do.
在伊利Z州法律授嘞
By the powers vested in me by the state of Illinois,
我正式宣布晌榉蚱
I pronounce you husband and wife.
您F在可以H吻新娘了
You may now kiss the bride.
先生女士
Ladies and gentlemen,
今晚有 莉莉安最鄣F演唱她最鄣母枨
here with us tonight is Lillian's favorite band singing her favorite song.
我用掌g迎威森菲利普!
Put your hands together for Wilson Phillips!
嗨,大家好!
Hi, everybody!
各位今晚安好?
How we doing tonight?
我才不要付@P
I am not paying for this shit.
?
Really?
@是最後一,我保C
It's the last one, I promise.
- 最後一 - 最後一
The last one. The last one.
我明白@N痛楚
I know this pain
何必拘禁自身於@N束`?
Why do you lock yourself up in these chains?
除了你o人能改你的人生
No one can change your life except for you
^不有心人阻r去路
Don't ever let anyone step all over you
只要敞_你的心胸
Just open your heart and your mind
感受其中不X得非常美好?
ls it really fair to feel
This way inside
Someday somebody's gonna make you
也S某天某人你
回心D意道e迷途
want to turn around and say goodbye
在此之前,H鄣,你要面
Until then, baby, are you going to let them
n愁拖B而痛哭?
hold you down and make you cry?
y道你不知道
Don't you know
y道你不知道可以D心境
Don't you know things can change
能再一天
Things'll go your way
快⒏S你的_步
if you hold on for one more day
能再一天
Can you hold on for one more day?
快⒏S你的_步
Things'll go your way
再一天
Hold on for one more day
你可以巫
You could sustain
是你是想c痛安然相宿?
Or are you comfortable with the pain?
然後找不到人Vf不幸
You've got no one to blame for your unhappiness
No, baby
只能身陷自_之苦
You got yourself into your own mess
就T多n]越^
Letting your worries pass you by
Baby
你是否J槭窃一改f^了?
Don't you think it's worth your time to change your mind?
No, no
也S某天某人你
Someday somebody's gonna make you
回心D意道e迷途
want to turn around and say goodbye
在此之前,H鄣,你要面
Until then, baby, are you going to let them
n愁拖B而痛哭?
hold you down and make you cry?
什N事@N好笑?
What's so funny?
我把上膛的放到小道的皮箱e
I put a loaded gun in Dougie's carry-on.
航管局扳_他的屁眼z查
The TSA is going to just rip his ass apart.
安妮?
Annie?
嘿
Oh. Hey.
晚上玩的_心?
Did you have a nice evening?
太美了
It was beautiful. Yeah.
X得婚Y怎N?
What did you think of the wedding?
太…
It was...
太棒了
It was great.
很棒吧?
It was great, right? Yeah.
太完美了
It was perfect.
很棒
It was great.
,很棒
Yeah, it was great.
可以到真的非常_心
It was really nice meeting you.
可以…
Yeah, it was...
海,可以到我也非常_心
Helen, it was really nice meeting you, too.
知道,也S找一天
Hey, you know, maybe
我三人可以一起去uL鬯
sometime the three of us could go to Rockin' Sushi together.
xx,安妮
Thank you, Annie.
芬其成
I would love that.
的子到了
Your ride is here.
晚如何啊?
Hey, how did everything go?
出奇的好
Strangely well.
那就好
Good.
我有吃的蛋糕
So, I ate your cake
x_後
that you left.
- 真的? -
You did? Yeah.
我得s走浣熊
I mean, I had to fight some raccoons off.
但不要o,我非常悍
But that's okay. I'm pretty strong and tough,
K]有太多的抵抗
so it wasn't much of a contest.
所以r…
So that might have been...
我F就要碛H…
I'm just going to kiss you now rather than just...
_警官,回…
Officer Rhodes, please report to...
我在糖
Oh! I'm on duty.
我要穿上制服
And I need to put my uniform on.
如果我穿@娱_,e人以槲彝稻
If I drive like this, they're gonna think I just stole a car,
不太好就是了
which wouldn't be great.
可以搭我的,意的
You could ride with me if you want.
- 想? - 我想
You want to come? Yeah, I do.
走吧
Come on.
好啊
All right.
要去哪?
Whoa! Whoa! Where are you going?
Me
I'm getting in the car.
- 不行,要坐後座 - 什N?
No, no, no, you got to get in the back. What?
不能坐前座,`反定
You can't sit in the front, it's against regulations.
快
Come on. Come on.
你要我坐後座?
You're going to make me sit in the back seat?
,戆
Yeah, come on.
抱歉,T了
Sorry. Habit.
算了
All right.
本性y移
It's a force of habit.
方便我坐前座?
Can I please get in the front seat?
真的不行,恐怕逃不^被逮捕的命\
Actually, no, I'm afraid there's a warrant out for your arrest.
槭颤N?
What? why?
危U{,yG垃圾
Reckless driving, littering, texting,
_用手C,酒後{
consuming alcohol while operating a vehicle.
不X得我r逃^一劫?
You didn't think I was going to
let you get away with that, did you?
Could we put the siren on? Please?
那可以_警笛?拜啦?
xx你
Thank you.
我明白有一N痛楚
I know that there is pain
但你芜^一天了
But you hold on for one more day
你x@束`
And you break free from the chains
我明白有一N痛楚
Yeah, I know that there is pain
但你芜^一天了
But you hold on for one more day
你x了,x@束`
And you break free, break from the chains
也S某天某人你
Someday somebody's gonna make you
回心D意道e迷途
want to turn around and say goodbye
在此之前,H鄣,你要面
Until then, baby, are you going to let them
n愁拖B而痛哭?
hold you down and make you cry?
y道你不知道
Don't you know
y道你不知道可以D心境
Don't you know things can change
能再一天
Things'll go your way
快⒏S你的_步
if you hold on
好了
Okay. Umm...
@是第119
This is Tape 119.
空警阿和我第一次性劢
Air Marshall Jon and I's first sexual encounter.
有一b|I的熊?
Is there a hungry bear anywhere?
我是|I的熊
I'm a hungry bear.
我恰好有熊熊三明治
I just happen to have this bear sandwich.
有|I的熊?
Is there a hungry bear?
我是非常|I的熊
I'm a very hungry bear.
看到我怎N翻尤馄?
Did you see how my flap opens?
有,那是不e看的熊熊三明治
Yeah, that's a good-looking bear sandwich.
啦,正是大熊熊三明治
Yeah, that's a big bear sandwich.
- 你想咬一口三明治? - j我
Do you want a bite of that sandwich? Feed me.
有肉和起士
It's meat and cheeses.
Uh-Oh.
希望你]有沙拉
I hope you don't have a salad. Oh, yeah.
猜怎N著,是火腿
Hey, guess what. Guess what, ham.
嗑了它
Fuck it up.
我要把你嗑了,火腿奶奶
I'm gonna fuck you up, ham nipple.
火腿奶奶,嗑了它
Ham nipple. Fuck it up.
有c痛
A little hard.
OW!
有c痛,有c痛
A little hard. A little hard.